lil tell you a tale of the bottomless blue
൧൧ ഖര്ഥ ഘ്ടക്ഥ ാദറ്ടനഥ 4590 (ഗ്രെ റ്(ഒന ൬൭൧൮ ൧7.
And it's, hey to the starboard, heave-ho
൧) ൨(ഒ൧, ല്‍ (൭ 2779 (കഥ, ൭൧൭.
Look out, lad A mermaid be waiting for you
ഖു, നഖ കല്യ കഥ റ്റ സലഥറ്റഥ ൪൧.
In mysterious fathoms below
27 റ്3ടഒ൦)ക്ഥറ്റ ഒന! റ്൭(൭൩൧൨൮)൭.
Isn't this great? The salty sea air, the wind blowing in your face.
ധിന്വിയ്ന ബ്‌ ലാ? ഘൃ ൮ നടന, ന നല്ഥാ ഠ। സ്ധ്ര ത്വ.
- A perfect day to be at sea. - Oh, yes, delightful.
-ിത്നാാടിധന്ധിധ്ം ഠി. - ഠപുര, നഘ്യഠണാത്ല്ത്ന.
A fine strong wind and a following sea.
൧ഗ്1൩ാാധടണാഭ്നോ ബിദ്ധ്ത്നാ നനണഞ്ച്വ.
King Triton must be in a friendly type mood.
മച്യ ന നസ്ധബുദ ല്ാലമടദറ 0 ടല്യി.
- King Triton? - Ruler of the Merpeople, lad.
ല്യം സ്ന? - ണലിന്ല ഥു, നപ
Thought every good sailor knew about him.
൧൮ ടാനാര ടന്ധട ല്‍ ൮ ലിവല്ഡ ന്മ.
Merpeople.
ഉധുഡയാ.
Eric, pay no attention to this nautical nonsense.
പ്പ വ്ത്ധിത്ന ടാഡ നഡ്വാലദുനഡ.
But it ain't nonsense. It's the truth.
ല്ലാ ബിധാധിത്നിഖഡ് നമ്‌. ബി നണമബാലാണ്ട..
I'm tellin’ ya. Down in the depths of the ocean they live.
൧ഡാം്ല്ഡ ത്വ. ൧ ്ടടദ്ധ്് ൮ ഠ്ലടണ ൭ ന്പാമ നല്ട്യ 093.
In mysterious fathoms below
27 റ്3ടഒ൦)ക്ഥറ്റ ഒന! റ്൭(൭൩൧൨൮)൭.
His Royal Highness, King Triton.
ദധബിവമാ ണദ്ധ്്ധം, ല്ല ൩൦൩.
And presenting the distinguished court composer,
ഉ നന്പല്ടാദ്വിത്ന രന്പാടല്‌ ഠ। ടന്ന ഭി,
Horatio Felonious Ignacious Crustaceous Sebastian.
റം ൦ലിംബവട ഉന്മഠിട ഠബട്ടംവട ലാട.
I'm really looking forward to this performance, Sebastian.
എവ നിം ന്ധ ലട ലി, ടലോമട്ിദ്ന.
Your Majesty.
വമ്ബിവ.
This will be the finest concert l have ever conducted.
ബിദ്വ്ര്ടണനണ॥ടലര! ൮ ലിവ ടര ാന്വ്ബിത്വ.
Your daughters, they will be spectacular.
൧10 വാലഭന്വാധന സ്മ്ബിവ, നല്ട്യ ലസ്ധ ലാഖ്‌.
Yes.
ഒ.
- And especially my little Ariel. - Yes, yes.
- ലാവ്സിലാനില! ന്ല്വഭം॥വ കില. ര.
She has the most beautiful voice.
വാസ ട്യാധ്സ്ധ്ലം
If only she'd show up for rehearsals once in a while.
ദ്രിദ്ധില ഠിഃ ഠ്ദ്ബാ ധ്ധിലാലിലിറ ടല്‍രി। ടലയഒ.
Ah, we are the daughters of Triton
൧൧, (൭൩൭൧0 ഒറ൭:ഥലഘസ്വാഥമ്ഥ 770൨.
Great father who loves us and named us well
2൭൧0൭ ഗലാദ്ക്ഥറ്റ ദേഷ്‌ ൫൩ റ്റെ നല്ഥാല്ത്ഥ (രബ ഗനട
Aquata
ീറ്ധ്ട
Andrina
൧ഥഠ്ന്ഗ0൭
Arista, Attina
൧൧5൭, ൧0൭
Adella, Alana
൧ഠല൭, .൧:൭0൭
And then there is the youngest in her musical debut
ഥു (ചനഥവ്റ ഥു നറ ടല്ധ്‌, റ്ദ(ഒന നധഷ്‌൭ ലന.
Our seventh little sister We're presenting her to you
൧വ്ലഭഥ്‌ ഒ) ൭ഥറ ൪ ഥാ ക ഥാലടലന്ഥക്ഥവഭ ;ക്വാടഠ്ഖനഥ
To sing a song Sebastian wrote Her voice is like a belf
ഗ്രധലനബെരഥ്‌ ഒറ ഥെ ലാട ഥെഥുഭ നന (ഠലെറ്റ
She's our sister Ari...
൧൭൭0 ടദഥ്ടട (൭൩ ൧൧...
Ariel.
൧ഥില.
Ariel, wait for me.
൧, ഡന്യാധ വ.
Flounder, hurry up.
നാല, ലോല.
You know I can't swim that fast.
ദ്ധ ലസ വ ലധാംല്പാല്ടന്മാ ലോട്‌.
There it is.
൮ ഠി.
Isn't it fantastic?
8ധിയ്വിയ്ന ബ്‌ ലാഖ്‌ ടലയി?
Yeah, sure. It's great. Now let's get outta here.
ര നണ. ലാട ടട്യി. ലിയാ ന്മ്ഥില്വിന്ടാബ്യ്‌.
You're not getting cold fins now, are you?
ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വുദഠി ഡന്‌?
Who, me? No way.
ട്ട, മിവ? നില ടലര!!.
It's just... It looks damp in there. Yeah.
റവന ന്ഥി... 1്ബാലാ ട൦0॥൨ഠ] ടിബി. “9.
And I think l may be coming down with something.
൧0 0ഠ്ബിവ ടം നേന 9 ടലഠ്ല്യാ.
I got this cough.
൧൮ ഠ്ല്വാദ്ലാമ്ധിംബി.
All right. I'm going inside.
810൭൩. ൧൮ ന നടടഥിലിഭ ഠ്ല്ദണ.
You can just stay here and watch for sharks.
ദ്ധ ഘാ! ഠിട്ലി ട്വ ൦0 ഡന്ഠാധയണബണ ഠ്‌.
OK. Yeah, you go. I'll stay and...
൭ അ, ത്വ ലായ. ചവ സ്ഥാ 60...
What? Sharks? Ariel.
൧൭ പല ഷീല.
Ariel, l can't... l mean...
ഷീല, ൧൮ വാ... 'ഗ്ലിഭ്ധഠിവ...
Ariel, help.
൧൧, 101൦.
- Oh, Flounder. - Ariel.
- ൨൨, 0ിംന്ല്‌. - ഷില്‍.
Do you really think there might be sharks around here?
ദബബിത്വിത്ധറി ന്ധ്ിന്ന ഠ്ല്യ്ഥാടിട്ല്‌?
Flounder, don't be such a guppy.
ലല്ല, നബി ടടലരല ത്ഥ !ഠിഠിം.
I'm not a guppy.
൧ഡാാധിത്ിത്റിില
This is great. I mean, I really love this.
ബി ധട ടയ. [ഴീല്ഴ്ധഠിവ, ടവ ടധിയാലല ബ്‌.
Excitement, adventure, danger lurking around every corner.
(ഭട. ഹാബൂസ്പാലമണ, ചിര ഠ। ടഖ്ലാ॥വ.
Ariel.
൧ഥില.
- Are you OK? - Yeah, sure. No problem. I'm OK.
-!ര്ര്ധവാദ്ിറ്‌ - ൭ ലന്ധസ൭. 1139 നടടില. ചവ ലി
Oh, my gosh.
൭൨, ഡല ലാണു.
Have you ever seen anything so wonderful in your entire life?
ലെല്വ്ത്വിത്ധന്മ ടംട്ധ്ബ ടല ബ ലിന ടല്ധഡ് വഠ്ലോസ്ധ?
Cool. But what is it?
സിം ല്യാി ല്വാ്ഖ്വ്ധ?
I don't know, but! bet Scuttle will.
ചവ ്ല്റവല്ഡ, ദ്വി ടവ മടി ടഗ്വേം ചത ട്ബ.
What was that? Did you hear something?
൧ ബാ ദ്ധ ഠ്ബുല ല്ലാ?
- [wonder what this one is. - Ariel?
- ൧്യാട്യ്സുത്ഥാ ബ്‌ മാല. - ഷീല?
Flounder, will you relax?
നാല, ാഠില്വ്യ്വിദ്ധാണല്മ്?
Nothing is going to happen.
11909 ല്വാദ മിന്വ ഥാലിമിവ.
Shark. We're gonna die.
ത്യാ. !ശ് ലിത്ഥ നി.
Oh, no.
ഠപ്ണാ൦ണ.
You big bully.
!ദ്ധവാബുമഠദ്ധാട്മ്.
Flounder, you really are a guppy.
ംഥ0ഠിലപാബ്ധിലറ വ ടലല്യിയ്ബിിം
lam not.
൧ിഡവാധിത്ന.
Fourteen hundred and ninety-two
ക്ലഥഥ ലന്യാദ 7൭൧5 ടലനഥ(റെ ാഥ്ഥ ൨൧൭.
Scuttle.
ധി.
Mermaid off the port bow.
1111] ഠി ന്ന്ിയ്വാ ടലാലദ്വവാല്ലാധിന്ന.
Ariel, how you doin’, kid?
൧൧ല, ഹാട്റുമ്നടന്മയ്ധ, ന്റ
- What a swim. - Scuttle, look what we found.
-൧ിബാ(ഖ്ന്ഘാദസസട നാല. - ഗ്ല, ഠം ല്വായ്പ്വധന്പാമ.
We were in this sunken ship, and it was really creepy.
ദരി ഠ്ല്ണ യ്വാലി ദത ഹാല, ൦ ഥാ നസഭഘസ്ത്ന.
Human stuff, huh? Hey, let me see.
ദംാറാല നടി? റല, 1 മവ ബു
Look at this.
1ന്യ൦0ല ബി.
This is special. This is very, very unusual.
ബടെ. ബി ടഥ്ാാധ്വ്ധല ഒട.
- What? What is it? - It's a dinglehopper.
- യാ? ൧്യാലിത്്ധ? - നില ഠിന്യില്ല്ല്ാല.
Humans use these little babies
ഗിംബസ്ടിട നന്യാധ്മ്വാബ്ട ഭി ൩
to straighten their hair out.
ധ്ധിനല്ധസടിക് ബ്ബാധ്നലല്‍യ.
See? Just a little twirl here and a yank there and violee.
1ന്യം൦റ ഥ്വട് ട൦൦॥ഠ] ട്‌ ഉ ിറി ട്ട ഠ്ിന്തില.
You got an aesthetically pleasing configuration of hair
ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വാദ ടബ്൨ ട്വ വാധ്വ നട്ടി
that humans go nuts over.
൮ ണട്‌ ഠിടധിരി ൦൨ നബ്വടദ.
A dinglehopper.
൧ന്ഠില്്ല്ാല.
What about that one?
ാറുല്നമന്മാധിട ഠുത്ാസ്പ
This I haven't seen in years.
൧0 ല്ല്ഥട്ഥന ട്വ ലവം.
This is wonderful.
ബി ടഥ്ാാധ്‌റ ണിം
A banded, bulbous snarfblatt.
ഒലലയ ടീ ൮ ഹാഖ ബോധി.
Now, the snarfblatt dates back to prehistorical times
ഗാഗ്ഥിദ്ധാടി! ഖാ മനമ -ടല്ധലി
when humans used to sit around
01 ന്വടിട സ൭ ്ഠ്ധിം
and stare at each other all day.
നല്ദഗ്ധാ ടടടണ്മ നല ടല ന.
Got very boring.
ന്ധ നലഘ്ര ന്വിഗധംടണ.
So, they invented this snarfblatt to make fine music.
ട്9ഠി, നലല നലട്ഷ്‌ ടാ! ധന്ധിനന്ബാധമ നസ്ധമിറവുത്ാനട്ത്ധ.
Allow me.
മ്ലിത്വ ദിവ.
Music.
ഗ്ധമി
- It's stuck. - Oh, the concert. Oh, my gosh.
- 9 1ലടധ്ാഖ്‌. - ൨൨൭൦. ൨൨൨04
- My father's gonna kill me. - The concert was today?
- 8ല്വാല്വ മയ്ബാധന്ധി ലിവ. - നടബ്ധിഘി ബ്‌?
Maybe you could make a planter out of it.
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൩ത്ധ ൦16൨ 10ന ടടടധബ്൨ ഠ। ടിസ.
I'm sorry. I've gotta go. Thank you, Scuttle.
ഗീ. ൧൮ നടട॥ 0൦൭. ലിനാ ൭51, ടഗ്ഥിട.
Any time, sweetie. Any time.
8॥-0॥ട ട്വ, ടു. 89-01 ട്വ.
Yes, hurry home, Princess.
൭, ലോബ്വാധിാ, ൧൨൭൨.
We wouldn't want to miss old Daddy's celebration, now, would we?
[ഗ് 151 നല്ഡ ക്വ ഗലഖയമ്ാല്വാന്മ, ഖന?
Celebration, indeed.
൨510, ാല്ഖയാബില് ലെ.
In my day, we had fantastical feasts,
ടി മന ലിവ, ൩ ്ടഖസ്ധണു്നാ നന്യിയധ്ിത്ഥം,
when I lived in the palace.
ടല്നടടാ ടവ ന്ന്യാല്‍ ഠട്ന്ട.
And now look at me.
ഉ ടലയന്വബാ ൦1091 ലിവ.
Wasted away to practically nothing.
[ഴില്മന്മ ട്വ! 151: നഠണ ട്വാ3.
Banished and exiled and practically starving,
ടി ഠ്‌ ധനാ ലി ൩ ഭ്വധിഥ്ന ടലാല്ുമം,
while he and his flimsy fish folk celebrate.
ടലനലന്മ് ഠി ൦ ൦-൦ യ്യാ ണ്സഡ്ധാണ്ടിയറി.
Well, I'll give 'em something to celebrate soon enough.
ലനാ, ൯13ാലിത് നല ട്വ ധസ്ധിറ്നഖ്ത്ടി്ല്ടണനട ൮.
Flotsam. Jetsam.
6ഠ്ടാന. പഖ്ടാണന.
l want you to keep an extra close watch
എവ ന്ധ ത്ധ നുമ്മട ലാലിലാലി
on this pretty little daughter of his.
ഒ03വാലഭന്ഥ്ധന േസിസുദ്ഖ.
She may be the key to Triton's undoing.
൧19 സ്ഥാാമ്പദഠി ഥന ഭ്യബ്ധ്മ്ന ന.
I just don't know what we're going to do with you, young lady.
എവ ലിവല്ഡ ല്വാദന്മം 0൭ ഠന്യന്്ധ, 3ഠിട സ്വഠ്ദ.
I'm sorry. I just forgot.
ഗീത ടമ൭. ദര ധ്വാദ.
As a result of your careless behavior...
എനാ ലാബാധമ്മത്ധവന ബട...
Careless and reckless behavior.
ലല്ല ദത ഡി! കലവര.
..the entire celebration was...
..ടല്ധഡ്വ്ാലയരാ്ഖ ലി...
Well, it was ruined. That's all. Completely destroyed.
൭ ഠ്ല്നന്മ്ഥഥെ. ടല. ലേ ടണം ടല.
This concert was to be the pinnacle of my distinguished career.
[ധനടണബ ടലാദ്ധബുദ ഭന്ധനലിഥാഹാല്വാല്മബിഡെ നാ.
Now, thanks to you, I am the laughingstock of the entire kingdom.
ടലയ്വാ, ന്ദ രടിവില്വര്ാഠ്ം ന്ധ, ടലി നാട്ട 9൦10൭0 മിവ.
But it wasn't her fault.
ല്ല ധിത്ഥ ടലില്സ്.
Well, first, the shark chased us.
ടാ സ്ധിബുയപ്ഥാ സ നഘാല്ല ത്മ.
Yeah. And we tried to... but we couldn't, and he...
൭. ദ്ബ്യഖണി ബോ സ്വിം. ദ്വ ൭10ലഠിലി, ഠ്ക0 919...
And we... And then we were safe.
ഉഖ്ബ... ൧0 ഭസ്ധഠിദ്സിത്മ്്‌ ടലടനദ.
Then this seagull came, and it was, "This is this and that is that..."
ന്ധ ഠാ ലം വ്യ, ദ്ദ ഠി, "ബി ബി...”
Seagull? What? You went up to the surface again, didn't you?
മച്യദ വഠ്ഖ്? ഷ്യ? ദ്ധ ന്ലിലഭ ഠ്വ! ൮?
- Didn't you? - Nothing happened.
ഡ്നത്ധാധദ്റ - നിദ ഒലി.
Ariel, how many times must we go through this?
൧൧ല, 511 ാല്ഘ്വായി ന്മ ഭന്മ ഥലയ്വാ ന്മന്ു ബ്‌?
You could have been seen by one of those barbarians, by one of those humans.
ദ്ധ സ്ഥാന ന ൦൦൨ ഷ്ാ-ംബാ [ല്‌ ഡ, ലീ നല്സ്ടിട ഠി ടമ.
- They're not barbarians. - They are dangerous.
-ഗീല്ലയാധിയ്ഥ റാ ॥ദ. -[ഗീല്ലയ നാട.
Do you think I want to see my daughter snared by some fish-eater's hook?
ദ്ധ ൨ ലവ നല്ലം മ്്ലല്വ 1ലടബാ!ധഠി നമ വി ാണലിഖ്ലിത്ന്‌?
I'm 16 years old. I'm not a child anymore.
ദയ 16 ലി്ഥ. ഭദൃയ്വാധിയ്ാധഠ്ട്ലാധഠ്ലലിി.
Don't take that tone of voice with me, young lady.
പദാ ദ്വന്ദ ബു ടവ, മനലസ്ധഠ്.
As long as you live under my ocean, you'll obey my rules.
ലയ! ദ്വ 09! ഠ്4ണദഥ്മ്ബിവ, ്ധാദ്ധ്വാദഠ്ദ ഹല്ധ്ബിവ.
- But if you would just listen... - Not another word.
- ലാ ൭ിദ്ധില മുഖ ബേല... -൧ിവ 11നദ്ധ ടലോഖ്ട്വാഥ ടി.
And lam never to hear of you going to the surface again.
ഉ ലിവ ടിനണല്ഡ ന്യ സ്ഥാ യ്ധ1ഭ ഠ്യ.
Is that clear?
പ്ല്ദടിയ്സ്ധ?
Teenagers. They think they know everything.
൧ഗി്ല്വാലടടക ടന. [ഴില്ല്യ 0൧3 നല ല്ഡ ടണ്ഡട.
You give them an inch, they swim all over you.
[ദ്്ധവാലി നല്ല ടദ്ധ 0൦, നല്ട്യ നമമട ഭ്യാദദ സ്വ.
Do you think I was too hard on her?
ദ്ധ 1൨ മിവ ലില്ധക്കട നക ഠി?
Definitely not.
ല്വ ടലയ!। 0051.
Why, if Ariel was my daughter, I'd show her who was boss.
ദ്രിദ്ധ കില്‍ 09 ടമാ, ടയ മഖ ഡബ്ഥിടിലാലാലിവടടമ.
None of this flitting to the surface and other such nonsense.
ലിമ ടൃ ാല്മ്വിയ്ഥ നല്ട്യ ൪ ഠ്‌ ബ്ബാല്ധമ്മബനബ്‌ ലാല ൮.
No, sir. I'd keep her under tight control.
1151 9ലയ. ദ ിത്ഥ ധി ഠി ാഒബ്ധി-ാബ്ബി.
- You're absolutely right, Sebastian. - Of course.
- ദ്ധ നണമ്യ ബി, ടലോമട്ിദ്ന. -ല്വ ടല.
- Ariel needs constant supervision. - Constant.
- ഷീല ാല്ധ ഠിധ്ടി ട്ടാ. - ൭ലസ്ദടമ.
Someone to watch over her, to keep her out of trouble.
[ഴി ഠി യാ നല്ഠാബുമ, ട്ധ്യാദൃദ ദ 1510്ച്ാമഭട്ധടല്മ്ന.
- All the time. - And you are just the crab to do it.
- ൭ലില്യാ നട. -൧ബിത്ധില്വിവ്ണലാബ്ുമാസമ.
How do I get myself into these situations?
റുല്നമന്മ മഡാഠില്‍ ലി ഠില്ണ !ഭഠ്മന ടലാബ്‌ ബ്‌
I should be writing symphonies,
൧൮ ടലാദ്ധസട നന്യാധാ ടിസ്ഠി,
not tagging along after some headstrong teenager.
ധിയ്ന്സുദ നാലര ഥലാലഘ്വാ ഒ04വാലടട ട്ഡസുത്ഥാ ്ലോ.
What is that girl up to?
൧൧൮൭൬൮ ഥലഘ്ഥ്ധ്ഖ നല്ഗ്ധമ്ാ
Ariel, are you OK?
൧, ദ്വ വാലി
If only I could make him understand.
ദ്രിദ്ധില ട്വ 0൦1600൮൭ ദ ലന്ണ.
I just don't see things the way he does.
ചവ ലിറ ല്ല ടലാബ്‌ ഠി നല്ല്‌.
I don't see how a world that makes such wonderful things
എവ ലിവ്ല്മണന 'ഭജ്വാദ ടലാധല ഥി നല്വു॥യ്ബാല്ദാലാട ലൃബ നണ്ടിം
could be bad.
0ഠില്വ്യടഠിരാധ്ഡിം
Look at this stuff Isn't it neat
20൭90 ൧ലെറ്ട ൨. ഥ്ഥത്ഥക്ക ൭൮൭ ദ്ധ
Wouldn't ya think my collection's complete
ന7ഒഗ്കറ (൭ഥ ഥലഥലസ്ട്യാ ൭ലഷ7ധ ദ്൭ഥ (ലറ്റര്വാ.
Wouldn't ya think I'm the girl
ന7ഒഗ്ഷഗ (ഒഥ റെ ഒധ ഗവ മ്ഥ്‌
The girl who has everything
14൫൨൮൭ )൭൨ ഒറ്ട ലഥ)൭.
Look at this trove Treasures untold
20൭90 ൧ലെറ്ട ൨ ലന. ൧ഒടഗ്ന്വാദറെ കഥ ഒഥലനട്റട.
How many wonders can one cavern hold?
൧്ലഭ്വാട ൧ഒറ)ഷ്ധലകഗദ്ക്ഥക്ക ഭ്ഥറ്റ ഒഠ്9 ഗ്‌ റ്൭(ഒന 590൧ ൮൧97
Lookin' around here you'd think
219 ഗല! േ്റല(ഒഥ)൭ വ്‌ 57.
Sure, she's got everything
7൧൭, വ്ഒ ഒറ്9 ടലന൧൭൧)൭.
I've got gadgets and gizmos aplenty
൧൧ ഒറ്ട 2൭7൭൧0-൧൭7൭൧ ദ്ദ ഠാലഒ(ഒറെ ൧2ഒ൭൧൮)൭ഗ)൭.
I've got whozits and whaizits galore
൧൧ ഒറ്ട 44൧ ററ ൧ ഖഥ)൭.
You want thingamabobs ! got 20
കഥ സനഗഥ ഥലെറ്ട 7. ൧൧ ഒറ്ട റ്ധഒ-0൧൧ഗ റ്൭ഥ൭0൫൭൧൮)൭.
But who cares No big deal
7ഒ ട4ഒ൧0൭9൧ ൭൧൮ 779൧. ഥ്ഥര്ഥവഭ ാല്ക്വഒ 295൭7.
! want more
൧൧ നഗ ൭൮.
! wanna be where the people are
൧൧൧ നഗ ഥല്യ്‌ (൭ 4ഖന്യാദ! ഒറ്ട നദ്ഗഥടഒ.
wanna see Wanna see ‘em dancin’
൧൧ ഥ൭ഥല്യ്‌ നല്ഗട!. ദ്ലലദ ലട നല്‌.
Walkin' around on those...
2ലു൭(ഒറ വ്‌ ൭൭.5 ൧9 7...
What do ya call 'em? Oh, feet.
൧൧൭1൭൨ നനു? പവ.
Flippin’ your fins you don't get too far
ലററ റ്൦റ്ുറെ 67077007 194നല്ഥദ്നഥ(ഥഗെ.
Legs are required for jumpin’, dancin'
ക ൧ഥഖബ്൧ ഗ്ധനലഠന്ഥാട! റ്റെ സനല്‌.
Strollin' along down a...
28ല൦5497-5൭7 വടലാദറ(ഒററ്റ...
What's that word again?
൧൧ാഠിയ്്വാലിത്ദാമ്സു്‌?
Street
പ്ഒ[ഒഥ7൭)൭.
Up where they walk Up where they run
൧7 (ഒന്യാ നലഘലക ൧ല൭(൭൨. ൧7 (ഒന്വയാദ നലല ഗാല.
Up where they stay all day in the sun
൧7 (ഒന്വാ നലലക ൧ല്്‌ഒണഥ്‌ ലാറ ഗ്‌ റ്(ഒന ഒഗദൃയഭ നദ്‌.
Wanderin' free Wish I could be
ഥ്ല്ലഖഥലാടട. ഗഗഗ ഒ സനഗഥ
Part of that world
്ലാദഗടറ്റ്‌റെ റ്ദഗ്ാദറ്ട റ്ഥഒ 440.
What would I give if l could live
൧൧൭൫൧൭൧ഥറ്റ ഒധ ൭9 ഥല്‌ ഭ്വ9ഥ൧൧൭൨ ഒ ഥഠ്ഥ0
Out of these waters?
(രല റ്‌ വാലെ ൧൨7
What would I pay to spend a day
൧൧൭൫൭൧൭൧ഥറ്റ ഒധഷഒ ഗാദയക്ധ ഗഥഥ്ഗഥ്ഥ്‌ ഹഗ്‌
Warm on the sand?
൧7 ഒട ൧൭5൧ )൭൨0 ൧൭൨0൭9൭7
Betcha on land they understand
7൦൭ ഗ്‌ റട7ടഒ്ഥ നലക 70.
Bet they don't reprimand their daughters
7൦ നലല (ഒനലഖക്റ ഒറഒലാലഷന്ഥാഥറെ നല്ല്‌.
Bright young women sick of swimmin'
14൫൨൮ ഒ-ഗ൭ഥവ്ഒ ന്ദ 24ഒ൪ റ റ നാഥ ാലഒറെറററ.
Ready to stand
28ലട5വ്9 ഗ്ധഥലയ്്‌.
And ready to know what the people know
ഥു ഥല്‌ ല്ട ഥഗഥ്ല്ഥഥ ഒ്രാ9 )൭൨റ ഒറ്റ (൭0൧.
Ask ‘em my questions and get some answers
7ഒവ൮ൃ൭ നല്ല്ഭ ട0൭(0ഥ ഒ൨൧ ദ്ദ ഗന ൦ധ്ട്യാദലബ്യാമഥവഒ.
What's a fire and why does it...
൧൧൭൫൭൨ ഒ്ഥാ7 റ്ഒഥ (ഭഥദ്ഥാട൭'൭൨ !൭...
What's the word?
൧൧ാഠിയ്്വാലിത്ദാമ്സു്‌?
Burn?
എ്ഖ്വാഖ്വ?
When's it my turn? Wouldn't I love
219 1൧൭ റവ ൧ഒഥറ്റരഗ നഗഗശ്ഭ ൭൨൧.
Love to explore that shore up above?
7970൧ നല്‌ വ്‌ വാദ്ഥ്‌ഖ്‌ ഥ്‌
Out of the sea
(രല റ്‌ [8ഗ്൭ഥ.
Wish I could be
൧ഒഥറ്റരഗ ഥഥഗ്ൃയഭ (൭9൧ ഒ൮.
Part of that
8ഠ0൭൨ 9൨ ലോദഗടറ്റ്‌റെ റ്ഒ0ഒറ്൭.
World
ഥു 4൧.
Sebastian.
ലാമട്ി.
Ariel, what are you... How could you... What is all this?
൧൧൦, 9 ൭... 8ദാല്നമന്മ ര്ധ 1൦1൦1൨... ൧൧൭1൪൭ ടന്വപബ്ുദ ല്‌?
It's just my collection.
ബബ ന൩൭ രില്‌ മവ.
Oh, I see.
൭൨, ലൃപ്ബ.
Your collection. If your father knew about this place...
ധിലയി ദ്വ. ്ിദ്ധില്വാല്ാദ വ 1ടഡ സ്ഥാ ന്വാമ ബ...
You're not gonna tell him, are you?
ദ്ധ (പിഠിഖ്വാലില്ഡ ഠി, ദ്ര?
Please, Sebastian, he would never understand.
1010൦00151, ലാട, ഠി മ0ലിത്ഥ്ല്ണന.
Ariel, you're under a lot of pressure down here.
൧൧ില, ദ്ധ ന്യ ബഖി്വലയന്മ ഠി ടബ്‌.
Come with me. I'll take you home and get you something warm to drink.
ഗി ബു ടവ. ല്ഡാദ്മാത്ധഖ വിണ ഠ്ബോലിത്ിത്ധ ന്ധ്ധണമ്ാ്ടട.
- What do you suppose... - Ariel?
- ൧്യാടിയ്വിത്ധ 2... - ഷീല?
Ariel?
൧ഥില?
Ariel, what are you...
൧൧ിലല്‍, ലാന ത്വ...
Jumpin’ jellyfish.
എനി
Ariel? Ariel. Please. Come back.
൧ഥില? ൧ില. 101൦0151. 8॥॥ലഭ ട്വ.
Max. Here, boy.
[ഗീ ൧ ട്രി, നല.
Hey, come on, mutt. What ya doin’, huh, Max?
ല്‍, നില, ബന. ൧൧ ത്ധാധദ്പ്ല്മറ്‌
Come on, Max.
മീലി, ഗി
Good boy.
്ധഠ്ല്വുമ്യാ ഖ്ന്ല.
Hey there, sweetie. Quite a show, eh?
റല, ടന. ഴില്ാിരാധ്സ്ത്്ഥുമ, ര?
Scuttle, be quiet. They'll hear you.
ടധ്േിം, റില്ല. ഴില്ല്ര 10 ഠബുല ത്വ.
I got ya.
൧വ്ല്മ്ണ.
We're bein’ intrepidaceous. We're out to discover.
ഗ്മ നന്പലദബിത്ഥ 0. ഗ്മ ഭ്ധല നല്ലി.
I've never seen a human this close before.
1 11॥1 നട്ടാല്‍ ലയ.
He's very handsome, isn't he?
൧9 ടഥാഠധ്വ്രംല്പത്ഥ?
I don't know. He looks kind of hairy and slobbery to me.
എവ ലിവല്ഡ. ടബ്വാട്സ്യ ഠി 9൭൦൩ ന൦॥॥൩ ധി ലല.
Not that one.
ധിയാ.
The one playing the snarfblatt.
ബാവാണ്ണദ്ന ന്യ ടന്മ്നീദഡ.
Silence.
8 :1111211:111
It is now my honor and privilege
ലന്നു ബുബാടട സ൭ ടമ
to present our esteemed Prince Eric
ഗലടന്ഡാല്മ്ന ന്ധം ൮ ഠ്ടബ്ധ്യി, ൧0 0൦
with a very special, very expensive,
ടല്ധ്ധ വു ണ്ട, ണന,
very large birthday present.
ട്ധ നഠി്വഘ്ഠി വത ണ്ട ടല.
Grimsby, ya old beanpole, you shouldn't have.
ദന്നട്മപത്ധ ടാവു 9151, ദ്വ 1ടിലാലിധാധബ്ാട്്.
I know.
ദയ ലിസ.
Happy birthday, Eric.
ലന 115190, 50൦.
Gee, Grim.
൨, ന.
It's really somethin’.
ബാബി നന്യിയ്ധ്ിത്വ.
Yes, I commissioned it myself.
൭, ടദുരുണാ ന്ഠാമ്വ്യവ്സദ ടാ.
Of course, I had hoped it would be a wedding present.
ന്ധ, ടാല്ലജ്വാറല്ലാബുദ ടിന നലഡ്വാലി ടദ്ധ ഠി ലിയ.
Come on, Grim. Don't start.
ചുഡ, ണ്ണ. പമ സ്ധി്്ണ.
You're not still sore because I didn't fall for the princess of Glowerhaven?
ലിറമ്ബിമ്സിത്ധ നടനല്ല ടലാലാ വം ഒബി ണ്മ നേന ലല്ല വിഖന്മണ്‌?
Oh, my. Oh, Eric, it isn't me alone.
൨, ടി. ൭൨, ല0൦ാധിഖ്സമ ടൃ ടട.
The entire kingdom wants to see you
ല്ലി ലുമ്മ നട്ധിത്ധ
happily settled down with the right girl.
വിഠ്ധ്വാവാട്നാിട ണന ടല ഡബിന് ടടട്ധല.
She's out there somewhere. I just...
ന്ധ ഠി ൭9 ഠി ടമ. ഭദ്ര ഡ്മ...
I just haven't found her yet.
ഡ്ധണട ടര ിധ്ഥന്ഥാ ഠി 91.
Perhaps you haven't been looking hard enough.
ഗ്ധ്ിന്൩ത്വ ടനന്ഠി ഠബുബാല്ഭാധ്-ടഥാഠാധ.
Believe me, Grim, when I find her, I'll know.
ലെയ ലിവ, ന്ന, ദ്വാദ്ധ॥ദ മിവഥ്ഥാ ഠി, ടവ ല്ലി.
Without a doubt, it'll just, bam, hit me, like lightning.
ലിഖ, മവ ടിക ലിരന്മ, ലു ടല, നന ഠിടാമ്പാല ഠി.
Hurricane a-comin’.
ദ്വാധ്മധ്ട നല.
Stand fast. Secure the riggin’.
ദനാ വദ. 'ധഖിക്ന ടണ്ഡമ.
The wind's all of a sudden on the move here.
൧൦ ഠനബ്യേസിാ-ാദ ലാമി ടി.
Ariel.
൧ഥില.
Look out.
പ്്൮ു2-992.
Grim. Hang on.
൨0൫൩. 8 ലു വട.
Max.
1-1
Jump, Max. Come on, boy. Jump. You can do it, Max.
1 ഠന്വാദ്‌ [ലീമ കവി, ന ഗ്വാ. ദ്ധ 0161, ഗീ.
Eric.
50൦.
Is he dead?
൧19 നദ്ധിത്ന?
It's hard to say.
വടി ന്മിലത്മ.
I can't make out a heartbeat.
എവ ലിഗഥാന്യ ഠ്്്യാബുസ്ധന്സഒ.
No, look. He's breathing.
15൦1 ൧9 ഥനണല്ദട.
He's so beautiful.
൧19 ഥാ സിം
What would I give to live where you are?
൧൧൭൫൭൨ ഒര്ഥ (ഥ്‌ ഗധ റ്റു ന്‌ സ്ഥാണഥ്‌
What would I pay to stay here beside you?
൧൧൭൫൭ ഒര്ഥ (ധഥഖ൭൦ ഗ്റ്ധഥാലടറ്ട വ്‌ മേ്വാഥറ്റ നഥ്‌
What would I do to see you smiling at me?
൧൧൭൫൭ ഒര്ഥ (൧ ൧൧൭ ഗ്ധഗഗട ഘ്ന ന ഥാടഠ്ഖഗ്‌
Where would we walk Where would we run
൧7 നറടക്ഗ ;ഗ്ട ഒക ഥലഒ൭(റെ ൧7 നറടക്ഗ ;ഗ്ട ഒക ഥല്‌
If we could stay all day in the sun?
കഥ (ഗ്ഒ ൧20ല ൧ല്ലനഥ്‌ റ്ദ(൭ന ദയ നല്‌ ലോക്ഗ(ററ ഗ്ഗ?
Just you and me and! could be
൧9൧൮൭ (൭൧ റ്റെ ഒധ റ്ദ്ഥ ഒ ൧ഠ'൦ 9൨
Part of your world
്ലാദഗടറ്റ്റെ റ്‌൧൧97൧.
Eric? Eric.
501? 60൦.
You really delight in these sadistic strains
ദ്ധാദ്ധിാദ്ധി ടിയ നല്ടടമ്വിത്ഥ ന്യുന ഠടേടലിയ്വ
on my blood pressure, don't you?
ഭ്വാദഠിദ ലദ്വന്ഥ ഠ്ടമ ടമുര,൭ണ?
A girl rescued me.
ലാ വാധഠ്ടലാലന്വാധന ടലി ടവ.
She was singing.
൧19 നബി.
She had the most beautiful voice.
ടധസ് നല്യ്ധ ടല്‍യ॥.
Eric, I think you've swallowed a bit too much seawater.
50൦, ടു ടാ ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വലദ്ന 1ലിദ്ധാബുമിലി ദ്ധ.
Off we go. Come along, Max.
1-11-11:
We just gonna forget this whole thing ever happened.
ഗ്മ പിഖ്ബിധാടിത്ന ട്വ ദ്വ ലില്ലല്ുടഠി.
The sea king will never know.
മച്യി്ധ്ിലിത്ന ലസ.
You won't tell him. I won't tell him. I will stay in one piece.
ദ്ധ ല0ലിന്ഥ ഥ്ല്ഡ ഠി. ചവ ൧൧ 1091 ൧൮ ലിഖ ബഠ്ധ്ാ ബാ ഠിന്0ഥെ.
} don't know when ! don't know how
൧൧ ൭ല൭ഥഥ ൧൧൭. ൧൧ ൭ല൭ഥഥ ൧ഒറുസറ.
But I know something's starting right now
ഒ ഖഗ ഒദ്ട ടഒടഥദ്ധൃകഥറ ഗ്രഗ ൧ാലന്നഥ്‌ഒ.
Watch and you'll see
20൭90 റ്റ (൭൧ ഒക്റ റ്ദ്ാദ.
Some day I'll be
കഥാ ഒധ ഒര്ഥ൭൨.
Part of your
്ലാദഗടറ്റ്‌റെ റ്ദ്ഥ്രാദറ്ദ
World
൧7൧൭൩൧.
Oh, no. I can't stand it. It's too easy.
൭൨, ൦0൦1൦. ചവ ലിഗം നല്ലി. സ ന്ധഠ്ല ടണ്‌.
The child is in love with a human.
ഗലി ഠ്വ ന്മ ന്യുന നബ്ടിഒ.
And not just any human. A prince.
ഉ ാധിത്ഥ ടലാല്യ നസ്പടിമ. ൦ 033.
Her daddy will love that.
പ്ലാസ ലിക ടിയ.
King Triton's headstrong, lovesick girl
൧ഗിലാലന്പാധ് ദലം സ്ഥ ൮ ഭട (ഭ്വാലിഃ ൦ നലാധിംല്ന്മ.
would make a charming addition to my little garden.
എിയ്ബുദഠി മസാല നല്ിധ്ധിനണ്മന ടവ.
Ariel dear, time to come out.
൧ഥില്‍ ടത, ലി ടാന്വാലി നടു ത്വ ഭ്ല.
You've been in there all morning.
ദ്ധ ഠി ഠ്ല്ടണ ട്ട 1 ടല.
What is with her lately?
൧൧൭ 951൩30 ഘ്യാഠ്സടഭ്വാല്ല്യ്ാ്ബ്‌?
- Morning, Daddy. - Well.
- ൭ല ണമ ഠാ, ൭. -[പന്വാമിസുഒ...
- She's got it bad. - What? What has she got?
- ൧ വിഭ ബിം - യാമ? ൧19 ഭന്൯ ലാമ?
Isn't it obvious, Daddy? Ariel's in love.
ദധിയ്വിയ് ലാ സം ചൃഖ്ന? ൧ഥിലല്‍ ടറി ലാലയ്ന്മ.
Ariel? In love?
൧ഗല? 8ല്യ്ന്മ?
OK. So far, so good.
൭ ടലി ബി 13129: ദ്വാ-ല്ാദ.
I don't think the king knows.
എവ ടാ സ്വ ലിന്ല്ഡ.
But it will not be easy keeping something like this a secret for long.
ലി ാധി്സ ടന്മ് നല്ലി ബി ധസ്ധിണടടത്ാ ണ്ട.
He loves me.
൧19 ലന്ത ടവ.
He loves me not.
൧19 151 ലിസ്ലിന്വ ലിവ.
I knew it.
ചവ ല്ധ്ല.
Ariel, stop talking crazy.
൧ഥില, യാ നലഘാലല്‍ം.
I gotta see him again tonight.
൧൮ നട്ട്‌ [ന്ഥ ഠബോ്സ ഠ! ന്ല്ണ ല്‍.
- Scuttle knows where he lives. - Ariel, please.
- ഗ്ല ല്ഡ ഠി നട്ട ഠി 09. - ഷിലി, ഠ്യ.
Get your head out of the clouds and back in the water where it belongs.
്വധലിത്ിഭ്യാദ ത്വ ഠി ഖല ൭൦൩ നടട്ധിടന്ധഡിട ൫ 2, 'സ്ഥബിത്ഖ.
I'll swim up to his castle, Flounder will splash around to get his attention.
൧൮ ടിയബാലഭ്മു ഭട, 0ിംധന്ല്‌ ലിന ഠ। ലലിറാണ്മിന്സുട.
Down here is your home.
൧ ട്ലില് ന്ധ സ്വ.
Ariel, listen to me.
൧൧ിലല്‍, നാല ത്വ.
The human world, it's a mess.
ബ്ദ നട്ടി ധ മലാല.
Life under the sea is better than anything they got up there.
ഠാ ഠി ടല ദില ലി ഖ്ലാ്മയ് നല്ട്ര ഠി ഠി മട ടന.
The seaweed is always greener in somebody else's lake
ജഥ്ഥാ൭ 8 5൭൭ 4ലാ77 ൧ഒ൧ റ്൭(ഒ൬ന :യ൭(൭ ടെറ (9൧൧.
You dream about going up there
കഥ ഥന്൧ത്ഥ ഗ്ല ഒട.
But that is a big mistake
7 ഒ 7ല (കട്ട്യാമ്ഥ 2൭5൭.
Just look at the world around you
20൭90 റ്ഗ്വ൭ വ്‌ ടലക്ഗന്ന.
Right here on the ocean floor
൧ 5൧, വ്‌ റ്ഒടഖ (ഒഥ്ഒ.
Such wonderful things around you
൧ഒഥറ്റരഗ ഗ്ഗ) ഷ്ഥറ്റ വസഷഗറ്നഥ.
What more is you lookin' for?
൧൧൭ (ഒ൦ )൭൨റ (൭൧ ഥ്‌
Under the sea
൧7 95൭൦ (ഗ്രെ.
Darling, it's better down where it's wetter
കദൃഥറ൮, (ലാ0 ൧൭൧ വ്‌ “ലനാ ൭൧൮ 5൭൭൭ ഗാല
Take it from me
൧ലദയക്ഒ ഒ.
Up on the shore they work all day
൧7 ൧ ൧൭0(൭ നലല ൧ാലഭ്ധുട ലോദ്ധ്റെ.
Out in the sun they slave away
൧ുഒ(ഒന ഥെ 4ഒനലഷഘ്ഭ ലക്‌.
While we devoting full time to floating under the sea
1] നാഥ്‌ വ്‌ റ്ടടല (ഒഥ്‌ ട9ഗഒ(ഒ.
Down here all the fish is happy
൧7 ൧൭൧൭൦ 5൧ ടലനഥട 7൭൧൮൭ ൧൭൧0൭൨൮൭.
As off through the waves they roll, yeah
൧൧൭൧4(൭ നലഘ്ഭ നല്ഠഗറ്റടഠ വ്‌ ഠ7ഥ൧ഖ൮ഗ൮൭, ൭.
The fish on the land ain't happy
4ത്ഥ വ്‌ റ്൭൭ 7റ്ഖഗ്ക ട്ര.
They sad ‘cause they in the bow!
ഴ്ലാദാ 7ഗ7ല്ല്ദ വ്‌ റ്ഒ(ഒന (൪൭൦൭.
But fish in the bowl is lucky
ഒ 7 ന്‌ ൭൦ 4൧ ഥലസ്ഥെ.
They in for a worser fate
എദ്ലലഒ നാറ്റ്‌ നട (ലാഥ (൭ഥ൧൭൧%.
One day when the boss get hungry
കദ[ധാഒ്‌ ൧79 20.5 ൧ല്‌൭.൭ (ഒ്ലാ൭..
Guess who's gonna be on the plate
ഗഗ്൭ഒ0 ടട) ഷ൧ഥറ്റ ഒക്ഥ ന്ഥ.
Under the sea
൧7 95൭൦ (ഗ്രെ.
Nobody beat us, fry us and eat us in fricassee
74ഒറ്ട ഥു ഥ്‌ 'ഗ്ട, റാറ്റ്‌ ദ്ദ നടക 'ഗ്ട റ്റെറുറെ (ധ0൮൭.
We what the land folks loves to cook
ഗ്൭൭0)൭൨ ഠ൭ഥറ്റ റ്൭ഒ൭൭ഥ ഗേ നഒട൭%.
Under the sea we off the hook
27 95൭൦ (ഥ്‌ ഒ !ഒ സക.
We got no troubles Life is the bubbles
ഗഗ്൭ 9ഠ്ദ ൧0൭ (൭5൧590൭. ൧൧൧ (ഗഒ ൧൧൦ (ഗെ.
- Under the sea
- ൧7 95൭൦ (ഗ്രെ.
Since life is sweet here we got the beat here
(രഭഥട ഗവ്ഥാഥൃഭ നട വ്‌ 5൧. ൭ ഒറ്ട ഖല.
- Naturally
- ക്ലനലനദെന്റഒ.
Even the sturgeon and the ray
4൫്ഥ (ഖന്ഥഥഗറ്റ റ്ഒഥ ൮൧൭ ൧൭൧7.
They get the urge and start to play
എഴലറ്ട്യാദ! ഒനത്ഥ റ്റ (ലഡട നല്‌.
We got the spirit, you got to hear it, under the sea
ഗഗ്൭ ഒഠ്9 നെറ, (ര൭ഥ൧൭൧ റ്റെ, വ്‌ ഥെ.
The newt play the fiute The carp play the harp
൭! ഥ്‌ഒഥാല്നമ്ഥ ല്ല 4്ഥ ക ഗല 70൭൧൧.
The plaice play the bass and they soundin' sharp
4൫്ഥ ഘലെന്നഥ ഥല്നദ്ഥ 2൧൭൭൭. റ്റ ൧൧)൧)൭ ൧സ്ര്ധ നെട.
The bass play the brass The chub play the tub
4൫്ഥ ട4ഒ൭ര്വാ നവെഥ്ഥ 4ലധന്വാല്‌. ൫്ഥ ഗഥ ഥാലന്നഥ 4൧.
The fluke is the duke of soul
4ഭ്ഥൃക്ഥറ്റ ഗ൮(ഒഥെട്യട (ഒറ.
The ray, he can play The ling's on the strings
൧ഒ7്‌, ൧04ലറ ഗലാ. 2൭൦ വ്‌ ഥാ 49ഒഥ.
The trout's rocking out The blackfish, she sings
4(൫്ഥ ലാട സനലക്ഗ്‌ 70൭. 4ഭ്ഥ ഗ്ന ന്ദ നല൮൭൨)൪.
The smelt and the sprat They know where it's at
കഥ ൧൭൧൭ റ്റ 7൧ ലേ. ദലലഷ (൭0൧ നെ 4ലന്യാദ[.
And, oh, that blowfish blow
൧൭൧, ൧൨, 7൭ഥ ൧0൧൧1൭ ൧൧ഗല്‌ ഥല്‌.
- Yeah, under the sea - Under the sea
- 1൭, ന്‌ റഖ 9൭. - ൧7 95൭൦ (ഗ്രെ.
When the sardine begin the beguine
219 7൫൧ മേ7ധ്ഥ നഥട ൧ാലന്നഒഥ.
- It's music to me - Music it is to me
- 77 നഥമഥറ്മധ. - മഥ 0ഒറ്൭൨൧.
What do they got? A lot of sand
൧൧൭ ൭൧൮ നല്ല്‌ റ്ദ്വാ൭7 ൧9൧൭ ൧൭5൧ )൭൨റ0 ൧൭൨൮൭
We got a hot crustacean band
ഗഗ്ട ഒഠ്9 (ഡ്ലറെ (൭൭൨൮.
Each little clam here know how to jam here under the sea
കല്യാ (കാമന ഷ്ഥറ്റ ഒഠ്9 ഗ്‌ 5൧ ഒ0ഥാലടഥത്ഥ്ട വ്‌ റ്ഒടട7 (ഒഗ്൭ഥ.
Each little slug here cutting a rug here under the sea
ക്ല്റ്ട്യാ ൧൧ )൭ഥറ ഒറ്3 നലന്ഥ൧൭॥ ഗഖന്ഥാലഒ വ്‌ റ്ഒടട7 9ഥ്‌.
Each little snail here know how to wail here
ക്ല്റ്ട്യാ ൧൧ (രഥ്‌ )൭ഥറ ഒറ്3 ഒല ഒട നറെഗ്യഡ്‌ ഗഖ.
That's why it's hotter under the water
ലാ 7(ധാഴറെറ്റട ഗല്ലാഗക്ഥ വ്‌ റ്ടടല (ഒഥ്ഒഥ.
We are, we in luck here down in the muck here
4(ഒഗാഒ0, (ഒന്ധാലലണ വ്‌ ൧ ന്‌ ഗ്ന്വാഥ വ്‌ ൧ ൧.
Under the sea
൧7 95൭൦ (ഗ്രെ.
Ariel?
൧ഥില?
Somebody's got to nail that girl's fins to the floor.
൭ടടില്യാഠ നടട്ലില്വാല്വിത്ന ട്രാ റടഠിട വ ഭഖന്ല്ി.
Sebastian.
ലാമട്ി.
Sebastian, I've been looking all over for you.
ടലോടട്ിറ, മിവ നല്‌ ഴ്വ നല്‌.
An urgent message from the sea king.
ദ്ധ ധ്പടറ ടു ഠ്॥ ല്ല.
The sea king?
മച്യ്പി്ധ്റ
He wants to see you rightaway. Something about Ariel.
൧1൭ നല്ധത്ധ ടലനഷ്വബാ 093. ടടധദ്ധ ലന്മന്യ ൧ഥില.
He knows.
81:11
Let's see now.
ഗി 1൨൭ 0൫2.
Who could the lucky merman be?
ടില്വാഖ ്ലഡാല്‍ടറ വാവ?
Come in, Sebastian.
[ഴീടധിറല, ടലാമട്്ല.
I mustn't overreact. 1 must remain calm.
൧൮ 00൦160 ലിലാ।ന്മന. എവ നട്ട്‌ ലാലനന്മനു.
Yes?
വ?
- Yes, Your Majesty? - Sebastian.
9, സധബ്വ? - ൭ലോമട്ിന.
I'm concerned about Ariel.
എവ ഡ്നട്വു ന്മ ൧ഥില.
Have you noticed she's been acting peculiar lately?
ദ്ധ നലന്വാമിഥാന്റാല്സുട ബു ടലറശ്ധാലല്യ്ാണ ബ്‌?
- Peculiar? - You know, mooning about.
- ദല? -ര്്ധട്ധില്നവസ നല്ടന്മ.
Daydreaming, singing to herself.
ദലിന്മയി, നബി ട്ടി.
You haven't noticed?
ദ്ധ ലിഗന്വാല്റ
Oh, well, I...
൭൨, ലിഖ, ടര...
Sebastian?
ലാമട്ലി?
I know you've been keeping something from me.
എവ ല്ധധിത്ധ ടണസ്പ്ധസ്ധിത്ന ടല്ധമ്ധ ഠ്്വാദഠ്ദ മവ.
Keeping something?
ഴിസ്ന്ബാഥസ്ിയ്ഥ ടടട്ധദ്ധ?
About Ariel?
ന്മാ ഡില്‍?
- Ariel? - In love?
- ഷീല? - 8ലയ്ന്മ്‌?
I tried to stop her, sir. She wouldn't listen.
ദയ ഡോ നടനല്ല, സ്വ്ബ്വ. 1ല്ല്വാ ഠി ല്യ്ാമ്ന ഠാ.
I told her to stay away from humans. They are bad.
ദയ ടി ഠിചദ്ല്‍്ത്ഥ ന ഖല ന്പട(ദ. 'ഴീല൭ല൭ ൮5105.
- They are trouble. - Humans? What about humans?
-[ഗീല്ലയ നലസ്ധാ് 319. -[ഗീ്പടി? ചാട ഠി ന്യ നബ്വടിദ?
Humans?
ഗിംബ്ടിമ?
Who said anything about humans?
ടില്വാവയറാ ഒ സ്ഥാ ന്ബ്വടിദ?
Flounder, why can't you just tell me what this is all about?
നാല, ഭന്വാലഖ്വിത്ധ 1ടിലത് ൩ ന്ന ല്വാദ ടലാലലസ്യ്‌?
You'll see. It's a surprise.
ദ്ധ ടിക ബും ബി ടടട്ധദ്ധത്റാ ടഠിടംാര.
Oh, Flounder.
൭൨, ലംഥ്ഥാല.
Flounder, you're the best.
നാല, ദ്ധില്സന റാലി
It looks just like him. It even has his eyes.
ബി നന ഠി. [ഗിസഭാഥ0 ടണമ.
Why, Eric, run away with you?
(രന്ല്വാം, 560൦, 90 ഠനണ്യേമ്ബിത്ധ?
This is all so sudden.
ബി ടഥ്ാാധ്നാടയിട.
Daddy?
ഷു
Il consider myself a reasonable merman.
൧൮ മാലാ ഠ്ഥിവ ടലാട! ഠ്വ ല്‍510ാലട്ദ നടടലാല.
I set certain rules.
൧൮ മ്യിത്ഥ ലാലഘ്വാാലയ്ഡന.
- l expect those rules to be obeyed. - But, Dad, I...
-൧ിവ നട്ഡലാല്ദ്ധമ് ബബ ലബ്പ്വ. - ലി, ഖി, ൭൭൮൭...
Is it true you rescued a human from drowning?
ദബബിത്വിത്ധ ടല്ണമിത്വ നടസ്ധടിട ഠാ ണട്‌?
- [had to... - Contact between the human world
- ദയ നാരാ... - ലന്ധാഥയാണന ഠി വ്മട ഠ്ഥ്ബിട നട
and the mer world is forbidden.
൦ ഠ്ധബ്ദ ലയന നവവി.
Ariel, you know that. Everyone knows that.
൧, ദ്വ ല്ഡ്ല. ലന്ധട ഘൂ ല്സ.
- He would have died. - One less human to worry about.
- ൧9 നലാഉന്മാഠ്ലാ! നദ്ധ്‌. -ഡ്രബാ ട്ഡ നബ്ഡ്ട ധന്ധിറബ്നട്ഘ[ത്ണ.
- You don't even know him. - Know him?
-കൃതനലിലക്ല 0 ഠ1ഒ. -[രരന്മ! ഠി?
I don't have to know him. They're all the same.
എവ ലിഥാല്ധഭന്മി ഠി. ഴില്ല്യ ടന്ധബ ടണട.
Spineless, savage, harpooning fish-eaters incapable of any feeling.
ദിവാലി, 1 ലാബിയ്ന ബ്ലാത്ത, 1909 ലാല്ദടമന.
Daddy, I love him.
൧൮൭൨. ടമ ലന്ത ഠി.
No. Have you lost your senses completely?
ഠ്വ 50 ബിനാ രി ടണട ടയ?
He's a human. You're a mermaid.
൧19 നബ്ധട(ദ. ദ്ധി ഠ്യ.
I don't care.
ദയ ലിലഠിട.
So help me, Ariel, lam going to get through to you.
പഠി 0൦൮1൭1 വ, ൧ിലി, ൧൮ നലിവുഖിന്സ്ത്നത്ധ.
And if this is the only way, so be it.
ഉംരിദ്ധ്മ്ന്ബ ടല ലേ, ലിലിത്വില.
Daddy. No.
൧൭൨ ൦൦൩.
No. Please.
പ്0൭൩. 71൦151.
Daddy, stop. Daddy, stop it.
ഷുര്്പാനണ്സ. ഷഖ്പൃണമ്ബ്മ.
Daddy, no.
ഷ്പ.
Ariel, l...
൧൦, ടവ...
Just go away.
ലലറ്ി ടല ദ്ര ട്വ.
Poor child.
ഗവ ന.
Poor, sweet child.
൧ഗനബ്ട ണാ നല.
She has a very serious problem.
൧1 ലാലന്നടടമിട[0 ടല.
If only there were something we could do.
ദ്രിദ്ധില് ത്ന റമ 0ഠ01ല0 0൮5.
But there is something.
ല്ലാ ഠ്യ 09 001൦00൮5.
Who...
ടദ്വാ3...
- Who are you? - Don't be scared.
- ടില്യായ്ധ? - പാന ടിഡി.
We represent someone who can help you.
ദ്ര ന്ലിറി ടട ൮ 001൦0 സ്വത്വ.
Someone who can make all your dreams come true.
൦0 0൦16൨ ല്വോി് ട്വ ന്വിബിത്ഖ.
Just imagine.
മചൃാത്ബില.
You and your prince.
ദ്ധ ഠ്ബാധ്യയ്ഖ.
Together forever.
ലട്രാനട ടലണട-1നബുഒ.
I don't understand.
എവ ല്വ്ല്നണന.
Ursula has great powers.
പ്രഭ്വി നബ്പാധസഖി വടട ടല.
The sea witch?
ഉധിഡ്ധ്?
Why, that's... l couldn't possibly.
(രന്ല്വാം, ധി... ൧൮ ടവല്‍.
No. Get out of here. Leave me alone.
11 ഠീ ട്വ. പദാ ബാധ ലിവ.
Suit yourself.
॥ഡട്ധിര ര്ധിട.
That was only a suggestion.
ഡമബുദ ടദ്ഡ മേനാ.
- Wait. - Yes?
- നാവ. ര്‍റ?
- Poor Ariel. - didn't mean to tell.
- (൫ടി൦ ഷീല. - ധി ടവ സിമ ന്ലധാല്ല്ഡ.
It was an accident.
ലട.
Ariel? Where are you going?
ഗല? ധ്ധ ന്ല്ധവഭണട്മ്‌?
What are you doing here with this riffraff?
൧൧൭ ദ്ധാധമഠി ടല ഠബോബാബുബാമ്ബ?
I'm going to see Ursula.
൧൮ ന്ലിഥലാല്യിധന്വാദ വ്ഭ്ധിദ.
Ariel, no. No. She's a demon. She's a monster.
൧ഥലല്‍, ൩. പന. ൧19 ാലടട॥[. ൧1 ഘന്വ.
Why don't you go tell my father? You're good at that.
(രന്ല്വാമ ത്വ മയി ൧ന്ല്ധാല്വാ്വ? ധത്ധ ൧0.
But I...
ല്ലാ ൭1൮...
Come on.
ഷുഡ്‌.
This way.
॥ഡ് ടി.
Come in, my child.
[ഴീ9ടധിറല, ലല്ഠിധ.
We mustn't lurk in doorways.
[ഗ്മ 1ട1വാഠില നസി ടലാലി॥ഗ്ന്ധ.
It's rude.
൮ ലിഗണമ്ബിട.
One might question your upbringing.
്യിയ്ധ ഠഠടടലിത്റ സ്ഥാന ഠി ടം.
Now, then, you're here
810൭, ടലന്വബാ ദ്ധ ഠ।ട്ബ്‌
because you have a thing for this human, this prince fellow.
ടലാദ്ധ ദ്ധ 9 0൫5 ധന്ധിം നട്ടി ഡ, ടി ഖ്ലിഗ്ല്യ.
Not that I blame you. He is quite a catch, isn't he?
ദധിയ്സദ ലിവ ടലിമ്വിത്തത്ധ. ൧ നല്ലി പിഖ്ഥ?
Well, angelfish, the solution to your problem is simple.
ഒം॥റ൩ തിവ ടദ്ണു, നസഘലിടടചിക നടടടില്വിത്ധഡ ടണ്ട.
The only way to get what you want is to become a human yourself.
സട ധന്ധിലത്ധ ഠ്ലാദ്‌ ലാ വ നദ്ധ,യ്വ ടാ നബ്വടദ.
Can you do that?
8ഠിലനത്ധവാധദ്ധാല്റ്ധ?
My dear, sweet child. That's what I do.
ദയാ, മ്ലഗ്നമ്ബിട. ധില്സന ല്വാധദ്‌.
It's what I live for.
ചവ വഠ്ധാക്ഥന്മ വ.
To help unfortunate merfolk, like yourself,
പന്ധിണനാമ്വ ധാ ൮ നടന, ട്വ നവ,
poor souls with no one else to turn to.
൭ നന്മ ന്ദഠ്ദ സ്പ.
! admit that in the past I've been a nasty
൧൧ ന൦െറ്റട(ധ സടടട റ്ഥ്ഥ, ഒ:ഡാധത്ഥവഭ ൧2൭൧൦
They weren't kidding when they called me, well, a witch
ലല ാഥത്ഥ ഥല്റഥ്ഥ ഒ്രാഒ൧9 ഗ7)ല്ലക ഥാ റ്ഥ്ഥ.
But you'll find that nowadays I've mended all my ways
7ഒ0 (൭൧ ഖര്ഥ റ്ദ്വാ൭7 ഗഗ ഒ ൭ഥാസ്ര്ധ വെ.
Repented, seen the light and made a switch
൧൭0 ൧ല909 ടഠറ്ല വ റ്റ റ ൧ലഥാെ.
True? Yes.
ബ്ബ? 9.
And I fortunately know a little magic
77962 ൧ഒഥഗൃഭ ഖഗ ഥഥ വെ ഗേ.
It's a talent that l always have possessed
കട ക്ഥഠലാദറ )ഒഥറ ഒ൭:൮ ഒട ഒറ്൭.
And here lately, please don't laugh, l use it on behalf
൧ വ്‌ ൭൧, ഗദാ ഗ്‌, ഥു (കട, ൭൨൭ റഥഗത്ഥവഭ ഗം.
Of the miserable, lonely and depressed
റഭ്ഥറ)൭൧0൭ നലഭ്ഥട, 2ഖലടഥെഷ്ഥറ്റ്ഗ റ്റ നഥ൦ഥറ്റ.
Pathetic.
(രടിഘ്സഒ.
Poor unfortunate souls
പ്ഡഭൃക്ഥറ്റ നഒഒറ്റ.
In pain, in need
4(ഒടശ്കഥ, ഗഗഗ.
This one longing to be thinner
കഥ ല്‍ റട'വ്ടധ്‌ (൧7൧.
That one wants to get the girl
്ഥറ ഗഥ സനണഗധത്ഥ ശവ.
And do I help them? Yes, indeed
൧ുഒ്ഗ ഒധഥാഥ്ഥക്ക നലല? ക, (൭0൧൮൭.
Those poor, unfortunate souls So sad, so true
പഥ ന൭(ഥറ)ഷ്ഥറ്റ നലദ്ഥട ൧. ഒററ 57, നനെ ലല.
They come flocking to my cauldron
ലല റ്റ ൧ല൧൧5൧ ൪൫ ഥലഒറ്റട'വ.
Crying spells, Ursula, please
ഗഒുലല൭൧, (.75ഥട, 4ഠഠ൧റ്റ.
And I help them Yes, I do
ഥുണ ഖധ ഥാ നലക. ൭, ൭൭ ൧൧൭ ൧സ്ര്ധ.
Now it's happened once or twice
ഗഗന ഥല്‌ ടലത്ധ്‌ ടല്ര'ഒ.
Someone couldn't pay the price
വഭ്ഥറുകഥറ ഒണണ്വാഥാദയക്ധാഖ്.
And I'm afraid ! had to rake 'em across the coals
ഥു (൭ടഒ൮൭ ഒ:ധ കഥ ഗാബ നലക ;ഭ ഒട ൧൭൭.
Yes, I've had the odd complaint
൭, ഒറ്9 ൧൧ ൭0൭൨0൭.
But on the whole I've been a saint
7ഒഠ ഭടല്ഗ്ഥഗകദ്ഥവഭ ഒധ ഥലയഥഒ.
To those poor unfortunate souls
4(ക്ാടഠ്ദ ന൫൭ഭ്ഥറ്റ നലഒറ്റ ഖബ.
Now, here's the deal.
ടലയ്വാ ബില ്ഷ.
I will make you a potion that will turn you into a human for three days.
എഡാധമിത്ിത്ധ ധാമ യവ നബ്ബഠി നബ്൨ടിട ടല 3 ജി.
Got that? Three days.
ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്ാദധ നാ ന.
Now, listen, this is important.
ടലയ്വാ, ഠ്യ, ൩ ഹാല്‌.
Before the sun sets on the third day,
ലോല്ധന ന്മല്‌ 039 0൭0 ക്വാ,
you've got to get dear old princie to fall in love with you.
ത്വ നടട്ലില്വാധമ്‌ വാമ ഗ്യ ധ്ദ്ധ സട ്ഹോദ്ധവ.
That is, he's got to kiss you.
1൭൮, 919 നടട്ില ല്ഥ്നത്ധ.
Not just any kiss, the kiss of true love.
ധി വന്ന ടന്പാലബാന, ണന ന്മ ടലബ്‌.
If he does kiss you before the sun sets on the third day,
പിയ ഠി ല്ഥ്നത്ധ ടലാല്ഥന നദ്ല്ഘ് ദ്ധ, നല ക്വാ,
you'll remain human permanently.
ധ്ധുഒഠി നട്ടി ടലണമ-1ണസുയ.
But if he doesn't, you'll turn back into a mermaid
ലാ വിദ്ധി വാഡ ധ്ധഠി ഠഥേയണ ടണ്ഡിദ
and you belong to me.
്്ബിത്ധ നിവ.
No, Ariel.
ട്ടാ. ഷീല.
Have we got a deal?
ഗ്ല ഖ്ന?
If l become human,
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലിഡദഠി നട്ടി,
I'll never be with my father or sisters again.
ടവ 10്ച്ാമ ട്ടാ ഖന ഠ്ക ട്ധഠ്ച്വിദാ.
That's right.
ധാ.
But you'll have your man.
ലാ ദ്വ ഠ്ല്വാദധില്ലറ ത്വ.
Life's full of tough choices, isn't it?
ലിഠ്ധ്ാ ബാബ്റി ട്വ?
Oh, and there is one more thing.
൭൨, ൦ ഠി ട്‌ 1.
We haven't discussed the subject of payment.
ന്മവാല്ഥ്സഥമ്റോത്ന സ്ഥാ വാദത്്ന.
You can't get something for nothing.
ദ്ധ ലിഥ്ലാബാബ്ട ഠബുബ്വാല്ധന്ട ട്വ.
- But I don't have any... - I'm not asking much.
- ലാ മവ മമഠ3... -൧ിവ സ്മ ലാസ
Just a token really, a trifle. You'll never even miss it.
ഡ്ധണട ടൃ ടല, ടമ്ധ ൭00. ദ്ധ ലട൦ഠിലാധസു്ാ ത്വ നാല.
What I want from you is your voice.
൧ ലിവ നല്ഡ വ്വ ല്ല ട്ധ്വ.
- My voice? - You've got it, sweetcakes.
- ഒ്ധമ്ജി്വ? -്ധിത്ധ ഠി, ട। നട്ട.
No more talking, singing. Zip.
1ലിവാഠില്വാലലിയ്വാ, നസി ൭൮. ലാട.
But without my voice, how can I...
ല്ലാ ബ്ാദ ടധലയിവ,ാടറമ്നടന്മ ടവ ന്വ൦..
You'll have your looks, your pretty face.
ദ്ധ നടി ഡ്വാ്ധ, ന്ധി ണല്‍ സ്വ.
And don't underestimate the importance of body language.
ഉംബ്യാബാാ്ഘാ ന്: ഭ്വാദഠിദ ഭ്വാഗില്നമബാല്നടാ ഡാധ്സ്ധ.
The men up there don't like a lot of blabber
വഷ്ഥറ്റ (ലഖ്‌ വ്‌ ഒ ട്ട (ഒ ഗര ൧ൃഷഥാലടഥല
They think a girl who gossips is a bore
൧ലഷസ്യാഥറ ഥാറെറ്റഗ്ന്ാമ ൧൭3 ഗലഒക, 7ല്വാഠടഒ്‌ക്റ.
On land it's much preferred for ladies not to say a word
27 ൭7൭ ലാഗ77 വറഖ ൧ലഖസ്വാഥമഥ 49:ഥലെഖഥലലരാ.
And, after all, dear What is idle prattle for?
ഥു, (ഒറ്‌ ൧, ടറഗ ൧൧൭൫൭൨ റ ൭ ഥേദ നല്ല്ല?
Come on.
1-111-11
They're not all that impressed with conversation
്ലലകാഥത്ഥ ലലെ ട്ഥകൃരഥറ ൧2ഒ൧൮൭ഥഗ്ക്൭.
True gentlemen avoid it when they can
2 ലഖ്‌ ഥന ല൭ഗ൭ഥ൮൭ 279 7ല്ല്ഭ 20൭൨.
But they dote and swoon and fawn
ദ്ലലഷ (൭07൭, ൧൭൧, റ്ദറ റ്റ
On a lady who's withdrawn
14൫൨൮൭ )൭൧ 4൭:൧നഴെഠറ൮ഠ!.
It's she who holds her tongue who gets her man
14൫൨൮൭ )൭൨0 5൭൧ 7ധ൦റ വ്ടൃഷ്൧ഥറ്റ റ്ദഠ൭॥ (ലഒഗന൬)൭.
Come on, you poor unfortunate soul
7ഒ7ഒ൦, (രഥ) ൭൧0 നല൭ഥ൭.
Go ahead, make your choice
ഗല, ൧൧൭ ൧൧നഒഥ (൭൧.
I'ma very busy woman and I haven't got all day
൧൧൧ലഘസ്വാഥമഥ ഥറുഷ്ധലക്്ട 1ഒ4ഥഠല ൨ഠ൧ഥഠ്റ്ഗെ്‌ 5൭൭.
lt won't cost much Just your voice
79: നറ ഗ്ര ഥ്ധ്ഗണഥ. ഥന ധഖനഥ.
Ya poor, unfortunate soul
കഥ്ന൭ നലഭ്ഥടക്ഥറ്റ നല(ഒഥറ്റ.
It's sad, but true
[ഒ൧൮)൭ ്ഥ, !ട൭൧൧ല്ഥ്‌.
If you want to cross a bridge, my sweet, you've got to pay the toll
പ്ര ഗഒ ലാലററഒനാദ൭ഥ, 6൭൭൧0, (ഒല ക്ഥദ ഗദ !ഠ.
Take a gulp and take a breath and go ahead and sign the scroll
൧ 9റ്െഥഒ0 റ്റ ഗാലനല്ടെ ലക്ഷ്‌ റ്റ 'ഒഗഠ്ദറെറുഥ (കഒട ൧.
Flotsam, Jetsam Now I've got her, boys
ഠം, പലരു. ലഭ ഒ:ധ റ്ഒ0 ട്രാ! വ്ഒ, ൧൭%.
The boss is on a roll
8ഠ50)൭ ടെറ റ൭7.
This poor, unfortunate
പഥ ന൭(൭൧൮ ൨, ൬൭൧൮ ലറെ.
Soul
പ്‌.
Beluga, sevruga
2ലഗ്ു൭, ഖഗ.
Come, winds of the Caspian Sea
797൭൧, ഒറ്റ (ഒഗ്ഒഥ ൭൭5൧൭.
Larynxis, glossitis Et max laryngitis
2ഒ൦ുഗാറ്ട, 05545 2 നവന.
La voce to me
ക്ല൭7൭൨൮)൭ 09റ്൭൨.
Now, sing.
ലയ്വാ, നസി.
Keep singing.
1ബടിട0നസുദ്ി.
That voice. I can't get it out of my head.
ട്വ. ൧൮ ലിഗംിബ്ബിധ്വാല്ഖ്്സ.
I've looked everywhere, Max. Where could she be?
ച്‌ ലവ്‌ നലല, [ഗീ ൧ നാന്ലിയറ ഠിദ?
Well, look at what the catfish dragged in.
8:10, ൦19 ല്വാമ ത്വ ൫ 9.
Look at ya.
1ന്ഠം0ില്വത്ധ.
There's somethin’ different. Don't tell me.
൧൧൭ ടടടധബ്ഡ്ാവാലില്ന്മ. പ്ദാബബാല്ല്ഡ വ.
I got it. It's your hairdo, right?
൧൮ ഠ്ലി ഠ്വ. ലസ്പാഥിത്ധ,?
You've been usin' the dinglehopper.
ദ്ധ നല്റാഥ്ന ഠ്ഘാ!ട്ഘ്വാഥാല്‌..
No? Well, let me see.
ഠി 85100, ല്‌ ലവ ॥൯9.
New seashells?
ധി ലാബ?
No new seashells.
119 ഡ്ധിഭഷ്ാ ബബ.
I gotta admit I can't put my foot on it right now.
൧൮ നട്ട്‌! നദിയ. ൧൮ മാല്‍ ഘുണ്സട ടലയഷ്ാ.
- If l stand here long enough... - She's got legs, you idiot.
-ര്രിദ്ധ മിവ ല്ലി ഠി ട്ബി ണന... - ൧9 2ഠ9 യറി, യവ 10101.
She traded her voice to the sea witch and got legs. Geez, man.
1 ലാലിയ ടധസിഭ്ാഠ് ഠ്ധിഡ്ിദ്ധ്‌ ഠ്ഷ ഠാ. ഗല്‌.
I knew that.
ചവ ല്ധ്ല.
Ariel's been turned into a human.
൧ഥില്‍ ൭൩൭൦ നട.
She'll make the prince fall in love with her, and he's gotta kiss her.
൧19 ദിയ്ബാധദ്‌ ന്ലിഗലപദ്ധ ണ്ട ഠബു്സട, ൭൦ ഠി നട്ട്‌ ല്ഥ്ന ഠി9.
And she's only got three days.
ഉ ദ മഠ9 ൩൭ 3 ൫.
Just look at her.
ല്ല ഠി.
On legs. On human legs.
ലിയ. 8യി॥ ഠ്യ ന്ബ്വടിദ.
My nerves are shot. This is a catastrophe.
പട്‌ ലിഡിഘഥ. ബി ടദ്ഡ നടില്ല.
What would her father say? I'll tell you what he'd say.
൧൧൭ മുരന൭ ല്ലി നബ? എവ ല്സ ല്വാ ഠി ടിക്ിയ്൭.
He'd say he's gonna kill himself a crab. That's what he'd say.
൧19 ൦൭൭9 ഠി നടവാധ്ഡ്നിര്ണ. ധിലി ഠി ല്ഖ്ിയ്9.
I'm gonna march meself straight home right now
൧൮ ന്മാ നിവ വിണു ടല്യഷ്വബാവാദ
and tell him like 1 should have done the minute...
ഠബബാല്ല്ഡ ഠി ടലാബ്‌ ൮ ല്വവാദ്ഡ' ടലാഃ॥ല്യമ...
And don't you shake your head at me, young lady.
ഉബ്യാദ്ിത്ധ ടിണ്ു ഭ്വാല്്ധ 0൭൮, ഡബ്ദ സ്വദ.
Maybe there's still time.
ഗ്രന ണടട।ന ഠിം നട.
If we could get that witch to give you back your voice,
ദ്രിദ്ധിമ്വിന്മ്വാഠില്‍ ന്മ ്ധ്ഡ്ബ ലാലി॥ഗദ്ധലുമം,
you could go home with all the normal fish and just be...
ധ്ധവാഠില്വാധിാ ബു ടസ്ധ॥ിഖ്ബടട ബുദ ൩൭...
just be...
19ഠ1 ൩൭...
just be miserable for the rest of your life.
19ഠ നല ടലാദ്ബുണ്യ ബ്ഠധാസ്ധവ.
All right, all right.
81916൩, 9091.
I'll try to help ya find that prince.
ചവ ടിക്ന ബോാന്ധിത്ധ ലി നല ഡ.
Boy, what a soft shell I'm turning out to be.
77൭, ലിിയ്നി സ്ഥ ഡ്ധിവ ഠ്ല്വദഠി.
Now, Ariel, I'm telling ya.
ലിയ്വാു, ൧൧, ലിവ ന്മ്വാന്ല്ഡത്ധ.
If you wanna be a human, the first thing ya gotta do is dress like one.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ന൦। നട, ഹാന ധ്ധ നടട്ലിമ്വാണാട്യികന നട നല്ടയ.
Max? What?
[ഗി ല്ലാ
What? Max.
൧൧൭൦ [ഗീ
Ya look great, kid. Ya look sensational.
ദ്ധ നലന്വാടറഘാദ്‌. നല ദ്ധ നലന്വാദ്ധ്ധനിദട.
Max.
1-1
Quiet, Max.
1-11-14
What's gotten into you, fella? Oh.
൧൧൭ ൭൩30 309 ൭്ധ ൭൨.
Oh, I see.
൭൨, ലൃപ്ബ.
Are you OK, miss?
ദ്ധി ലര
I'm sorry if this knucklehead scared you.
[ഗീ വയദ്ധ ടി ഠഠ൦ വ 1ടിഡിത്ിത്ധ.
He's harmless really.
൧19 1ടിലരാ്ധ ഗന, ടലാല്ലസ്.
You seem very familiar to me. Have we met?
ടാ സ മിവവാനട്വ്ധ്വാര്ധ. ന്മരാലന്മ്വാലിഥ്ഥാമ?
We have met. I knew it. You're the one I've been looking for.
[൭ 5101 ന്ധ. ലവ ലസ. !ദ്ധില്സ൭ന ലവ വി.
What's your name?
കല്യാ ന്ധ?
What's wrong? What is it?
൧൧ ിവരന്ട? ച്യാ ഠി?
You can't speak?
ദ്ധ 0൦0 ാലമ്യ്വാ?
Then you couldn't be who I thought.
പ്ഒഠി !യ്വധിത്വില ടിലാു ലവ ടയ.
What is it? You're hurt?
൧൧൭ ഠി ദ്ധ ല്‌?
No. You need help?
ലിധദ്ധവാല്ധാടന്ധണ്‌?
Careful. Careful, easy.
൨1-05. 1150-15, ലാല.
You must have really been through something.
ദ്ധ സ്വ ഠി നലാാല്ി ടട്ധമ്ബ.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
പനാ. ചവ മ്്ബാഖ്ധത്ധ.
Come on. You'll be OK.
ഗി. ദ്വ ടിയബാലിം
Washed up from a shipwreck.
ലയ്ലന്വാല ഠ്വ ധ്യാ! 0531.
The poor thing.
(൫ട॥ന് ഠിഒ.
We'll have you feeling better in no time.
ദരി ടിക ടസ്ബ്ധ്വത്ിത്ധ ബന ലോദ്ബുദ.
I'll just get this washed for you.
ചവ ഡധിത്ഥ ബ്‌ ധ്ധിലത്ഖ.
You must have at least heard about this girl.
1ല്വ ത്വ ഠ്ലഠ്ണാല 1ല്മഥഘാ 3ഠിട ബി.
- No. - Gertrude says...
- 11991൦ - ദപ്ധഠട ൭1൭...
When has Gertrude ever gotten anything right?
നല്ലില പ്പ ഠി ടല്ധ്ധവ ബി?
- Really. - Madam, please...
- ലന. - ൧൨൭0, 01൦൩11...
She shows up in rags and doesn't speak. Not my idea of a princess.
൧19 ലായി ഗന. ൦ ടിവായ്ലിത്വാ. ൧1 ലാധിത൦ ടന 0൦ ാ3ഠ്വ.
If Eric's looking for a girl,
ദ്രിദ്ധ റ നല ടട 3ഠിട,
I know a couple of highly available ones right here.
ചവ ശ്ന ാലാല്ല്വാദ ൮ ടടട്ധലി ടല ഠി ട്വ.
Eric, be reasonable.
50൦,൮90 സ്വന്മടലാല്വദ.
Nice young ladies just don't swim around rescuing people in the ocean
ദദഠിട സ്ധ്ാടിവട്ലാന്മു നല ൮ ധന്ധിഠിടംണ്ട്‌ ഠി
and then flitter off into oblivion.
ഭന്ധം ബിം ്ജ്വ.
I'm tellin’ ya, Grim. She was real.
വത്‌ ാദഠ9ധ്വ, 0ന. ൧19 നനണമന്റ 3ഠ9.
I'm gonna find that girl, and I'm gonna marry her.
൧൮ ന്ലിലി റുഠിട വ, ൭൦൩ 1൮ നല്ലത്‌ ഠിഒ.
Come on, honey. Don't be shy.
ഗി ടല. വബമ്നനദ്ധ.
Eric, isn't she a vision?
ലം, ഠ്യ ഠി നല്ല?
You look wonderful.
ദ്ധ്വാ്ധ൨ നി ടല്‍യി.
Come, come. You must be famished. Let me help you, my dear.
ഗി, നല. (ദ്ധ ന്ധ. ദ്ര്ല ടമാടന്ധിത്ഖ, ടമാ.
There we go. That's better.
വധ ഠി. ധിലാവാലിം
Now, quite comfy? Good.
ടലയ്വലാ ലി ടലിടടമ? മറ്റ.
It's not often that we have such a lovely dinner guest, eh, Eric?
ദധിന്വ ടലല്ധ 9 30൭ 1ല്ദസ്ധ ദേസിറ। നല നലിയ, ലിറ?
Do you like it? It is rather a fine one.
ദ്ധ ടധിര ബ്‌? ബിവ മാട.
Oh, my.
൭൨, ലി.
Sorry, Grim.
ഴി, ന.
Why, Eric, that's the first time I've seen you smile in weeks.
(രന്്വാം, 50൦, ഡയ ന്ന ഠ്ട്ണണ 0ലാലഘ്വാ സ്ന്റാഠ്ധ ടമ ॥നമത്ധ ടസുവണ.
Very amusing.
ധാധ്ന്ധല.
Carlotta, my dear, what's for dinner?
ച്വിണ്ം, ടബയ്നാവ, ലാട ധ്ധിനന്ല്ത്ന?
You're gonna love it. Chef's been fixing his speciality: stuffed crab.
ദ്ധ ടിക ടധിര ബ. നധ്ക നടടം നസ൭ഠിലക്ിഭ്ണ ടഥ്ാഖ്‌.
Nouvelle cuisine
795ഒക്ഥ ൧൭7൧.
, Les Champs-Elysées
ക 2ടെ ഗ0൭൬05-2)56ടെ.
Maurice Chevalier
ദ്ദ ഗഖ്ഷ്‌ല
Les poissons, les poissons
7൭൧, 7൭ഥ.
How I love les poissons
൧൧ ഒന ടഥ്ര 7൨.
Love to chop and to serve little fish
കര ൧ഠ!ഠ൧റ്റ റ്റ ഗറ്ഒഥറ്റത്ഥ 7 :൭ഥ7.
First l cut off their heads Then I pull out their bones
ഗ0ഗ9-നഥ്‌ഒഥ൮൭ ഒ:ധ ൧04൧൨ 7൭൧൭൭. ഗരനഥ്വ് ഒ ലഘാശ്കഥ 'ധറെന്സഭ.
Mais oui, ¢a c'est toujours delish
൧ ഗ്ര്ഥഗ, റെട!ലെ൭ട൭.
Les poissons, les poissons
7൭൧, 7൭ഥ.
With the cleaver I hack them in two
൧7ലറ്റ്ഗ ൧5ഒ൧ ഖധഥലഒഗ റ്ഥ൭.
! pull out what's inside and I serve it up fried
൧൧ ൭൮൭൧൮ ഗ്‌ ൭൩൮൭ റ്റ ഗഠ്ദഗറ്റത്ഥവ൭ (ലാഒട വ്റ്റ൭ററ്റ.
‘Cause I love little fishes Don't you?
ലാ ഒ ധര 7ക്ഥ-ഗര്ഥ (രഥ ഭഥ്വാഥ ഥല്റ്ഥ്‌
Here's something for tempting the palate
വ ട്േധദ്ധ ഗ്ഥധനണമൊഥ്ഭ ടല്ലട.
Prepared in the classic technique
൧5490ഭഥ റ്റു 7൦൭ (൭൭.
First you pound the fish flat with the mallet
ഗ്ഗ ;(രഥാഥ്ധ്‌ കഥ ടഒ7നയ൭! (ല്ഠാല്‌ റ്ാറ്റട്ഗ 4.
Then you slash through the skin, give the belly a slice
രഥ്‌ ൭൧ ഗഗ്ടര്ഥുക, ൧75കഥ 0ാലഥബ൭.
Then you rub some salt in
(രഥ്‌ 9ഠ5ഠ0ക്ഥ ടവ്‌ റുഖഖന.
‘Cause that makes it taste nice
ക്ലാ 74 നലാറ്റലറദക്ഥഒ.
l have missed one.
എവ നാടി ടദ്ധ.
Sacrebleu What is this
കദലഘാ!ലഥെ ൧൧൭ ൧൨7
How on earth could! miss
ഥഒറ്നക്ഗലര്ഗ ഖധഥഠല൦ (൭ ഥടസ്യാല്‌
Such a sweet, little succulent crab?
കല്യ (കന (ഒല നട ഥാറെഗ 26757
Quel dommage What a loss
൮൧൭ റാനനദറ്റ ൧ഒഥറ്റരഗ ഡ്നു൭.
Here we go, in the sauce
൨ വ്ദ, (൭ റഖ 0.
Now some flour I think just a dab
(രഥ്‌ ടവ്‌ 'ലാഥറ ഒ:൮ ട്യോധത്ഥ ൧൭൨൫൭൨൮൭.
Now I'll stuff you with bread
ഥുഒ്ണ ഖഗ ടധണ്ാ൭! റ്റെറുറെ 707.
It don't hurt ‘cause you're dead and you're certainly lucky you are
ന7ഒഗക്ഥ 7ടടട ട9ഗ്‌ ലോ (൭൧ റ നദ്‌ റ്റ (ഒഥ നലനെറ്റ ൧ലസ്ഥെ, ശ്ധ്൦ ൭൧.
‘Cause it's gonna be hot in my big silver pot
ട്ലാദ൧ ഒര്ഥ ന്ധ ാഒഥടടെ റ്ദ(൭ന ലററ ൧ല്ടഗ്ല.
Toodle-oo Mon poisson, au revoir
7ഠഠ൨്‌൭-ഠഠ 4൫ഥധ. ഗ്വാ (ഒ0.
What is this?
൧൧ന്‌?
I think I'd better go see what Louis is up to.
1111] ॥05 ലാമ ഠധിട 0൮5.
Come out, you little pipsqueak, and fight like a man.
്വധലിലി ടി ഭിധാബുഖ്ഗന്ധിധ്‌, ി്ബിദ്ഖറ ടല 03൨.
Louis.
1 ഠിട.
- What are you doing? - Well, I was just...
- ്യാടിന്ധാധമ്റ - ൧൮ ബ്ന...
I'm sorry, madame.
ഴീദലിദ്ഥ മിവ, ൧൮൭.
You know, Eric, perhaps our young guest might enjoy
ദ്ധ ല്ഡ, ൧൦, ന്ധ്ിന൩്വ സ്ധഠ്ംന്ട ട്ര
seeing some of the sights of the kingdom.
നല॥ന ട൦॥൪ നമ്ബറില്‍.
Something in the way of a tour.
ദലിവബ്ഥ്നാ ട൦൦॥൨.
I'm sorry, Grim. What was that?
ഗാലിക്ഥ വ, ന്ന. ഘാല്‌
You can't spend your time moping about. You need to get out.
ദ്ധ മില നാടക നടാ ല്ധ്ണ ടല. (വ നടട॥ ക്വ.
Do something. Have a life.
8 ടടട്ധദ്ധ. 8ലിര്വഠ്ധ്ാന.
- Get your mind off... - Easy, Grim.
- [ധാന ദ്വാ-ല്വാമ... - 91-00, ന.
It's not a bad idea, if she's interested.
ധാദറ്ധടധാദ, ദ്ധ ദ നട്സ.
Well, what do ya say?
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാവ, ഖാ ഖന്ധ?
Would you like to join me on a tour of my kingdom tomorrow?
ദ്ധ ന്ധ യ്‌ ട്വ നലാാഥ്ലാ! നലാമല്വ ടം
Wonderful. Now, let's eat before this crab wanders off my plate.
ദാറുധട. ലയ, ന്ഥന്ദ നടക ടലാല്ഥ്ന അണ ബ്‌ 1൭1.
Come here, boy.
[മീലി നടി, നലം.
This has got to be, without a doubt,
ബന്ധി, 0൭!
the single most humiliating day of my life.
ട്വ ൮ ണമ നനനല്ധിത്ഥ ലിന ബദ്ധ്ിവ.
l hope that you appreciate what I go through for you, young lady.
ടവ ന്മജ്വാത്ധ നഘാന്മ്യുല ല്വാദ ൮ ല്വാധദധസ്ധിന്ധവ, ഉ3ഠിട സ്വഠ്ദ.
Now, we got to make a plan to get that boy to kiss you.
ടലയ്വാ, 09 നട്ാധമ് ടാഡ 0൩ ട്വോാഖരല്‍ട[0 സ നലഘ്ധ്ണത്ധ.
Tomorrow when he takes you for that ride, you gotta look your best.
£ടഠധാ॥ദ ദ 0ധ ദ്ധ വായ! ഭ്ധല, ്വാ്ധ നടി നന്മയമ ടലല്‍ര!!.
You gotta bat your eyes, like this.
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ ഭ്വ്ലിത്ഥ നട്ടനസ്ധ, ലബ്‌.
You gotta pucker up your lips, like this.
ദ്ധ നട്ട്‌ മ ന്ധ, നദല്വേ ബ്‌.
You are hopeless, child. You know that?
ദ്ധലിഗൃധ്ന, ന. ദ്ധല്ധ്ധ?
Completely hopeless.
ലിഗ്്മ ടല.
Any sign of them?
൧൧൭ ദ്വ നന്വാനലഘല്‍്യ?
No, Your Majesty. We searched everywhere.
11ഠിമപ്ധല്വിധ. വ്രണ ലോ നല്മ്മ-മ്മ.
We've found no trace of your daughter or Sebastian.
ദ്രണി ലഗന്വാലിഥാഥന വലി 1വബിവ, ഖ്ദ്ധ ടലോമട്ി.
Keep looking. Leave no shell unturned, no coral unexplored.
0 ൭൮! വണ ാദിത്ഥ ടദ്ധിവി॥ ഭ്വാലി, മ്‌ ഥാ ഖാ ഠ്യ.
Let no one in this kingdom sleep until she's safe at home.
പ്ദ്നാ്ബാണ്മ്ത്ന ടടടില്വാ ഠ്‌ വന്യ ദ ധി ഠ്യ ടലണട്‌.
Yes, sire.
൭, സ്വമ്ബ്വ.
What have I done?
൧൧ ലവ ഠ്വ
- Has he kissed her yet? - Not yet.
- ൧9 9൭ നലഠ്ധ്സ? - 10911.
Judy.
പധ.
Yo. Flounder. Any kissing?
൨൦. 0ംധന്ല. ഠിം പധാന?
No, not yet.
1ദിപാല്ധ്ണ മഠ.
Well, they'd better get crackin’.
8ം॥ഗനല്ട്യ ന്ധില്്ന ടല.
Move over. Move your big feathers. I can't see a thing.
അലാ. ചിവത്ബാധ്ധാടെല സ്വ. ൧൮ മഗന്ന്വാലി്വാമ-ല്വാമ.
Nothing is happening.
1109 ല്വാുഖ്ബാവാലില്വ.
Only one day left, and that boy ain't puckered up once.
ലസ ടാഡ ലയ, ബബ്ലി ൮ ല0ല്ധന ടയ ൧൧൩1൭1.
OK. All right, this calls for a little vocal romantic stimulation.
൭ ഒം॥റഖ്ന്ബ നനണലിധിത്ന ടബ്ബ ലിലി ധാമ ണ്ട.
Stand back.
ബ്ന.
Somebody should find that poor animal and put it out of its misery.
8നമ്ബ്വണാ നട്ട ധ്യ ഠി ൦ ഠിന്മ്വിടിക്ന ട്വ നആ൭സ൭.
Geez, man. I'm surrounded by amateurs.
൨, ടിത്ധ ഠ॥ഭ॥ന് എബാ-്ണബാ വഫാ ല്ദ്വാ.
You want something done you've got to do it yourself.
ദ്രിദ്ധിത്ധ ന ടടട്ധമ്ബ ിമഡിയ്ബിത്ധ നട ാധമ്‌ ടറി.
First we got to create the mood.
ലനാ റ ന്മ ടക ടട.
Percussion.
ദസ്ിു്ണാ ഠ്ലാധിവി.
Strings. Winds.
ബാധാ. "ഷാ ഠ്യ.
Words.
ലിയ.
There you see her
൧7 ടല ൭൧ 0൭ ൨൭.
Sitting there across the way
൧ുറ്ഥ വ്‌ ലാല 590൭.
She don't got a lot to say
൧൭ (൭ഥാഥുഭഥഷ്രഒ.
But there's something about her
7ഖ്ദ്യാ7 ഒറ 59590൧ ഹറ൭ഥറ൦൭.
And you don't know why but you're dyin’ to try
ഥു (രഥ ൭ലഥഥ ക്വട്വാദ ഒ്ല7 (൭൧ ഥഖ്ഥാഖ്ഥ്‌ ന ൧൧൭.
You wanna kiss the girl
കഥഥല ലഗ്ന 7്ധഗവെ്ട.
Did you hear something?
ദ്ധ ഠ്ബുല ല്ലാ?
Yes, you want her
൭, (ഒന മ്‌ഒ.
Look at her You know you do
7ണറ്റഠശ്൭7 ൨൭. കഥഒഗഥരഥനമഥ.
Possible she want you too
ഗഗന ന്ദ ഥാഥ സ ഗഥ്ത്ഥ (രഥ.
There is one way to ask her
൧റ്ദ 59൧ ലട ഗഥ്ഥഖബ്െുര.
It don't take a word
79൭4ഥഖണ്ഥ (ക൭-൪൭.
Not a single word Go on and kiss the girl
79 ലോദഗ7 ഥാഥ. ഗഗ വണ 7്ധ ൭൨൫൭.
Sing with me now.
ഡയസ്ധിക്ബില്ലാല്ടണട ൭1൮.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la My, oh, my
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 ൧റ്ഥ൧൭ 07 ഒറ.
Look like the boy too shy He ain't gonna kiss the girl
ഗ7ഖന്ഥാട'ഗൃഭ സട (൭൭0 നല. 79 ല്ഗ്ന ഗവ്ഒ.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la Ain't that sad?
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 ഥഥത്ഥക്ഗ 7 ബ്ഗ?
Ain't ita shame?
൧ഒഥറ്റരഗ ടദൃക്ഥറ്ഗഒ?
Too bad he gonna miss the girl
കദൃഭ്ഥറ്ഗ)൭ വട ഖര്ഥ (കവറു ഥെ 7൧.
l feel really bad not knowing your name.
ചവ ലട ഭ്ന്ട ല്ഡ നന്വ.
Maybe I could guess. Is it Mildred?
ഗ്ധ്ി1ന്൩ ല്വലാംല്വ്ലല്‍൭. [7॥൦ഠി്‌?
OK, no.
്പാധിത്ഥ.
How about Diana? Rachel?
ദാറുല്നാന്മ ഠാ ഥടന്മ്‌? ദല?
- Ariel. Her name is Ariel. - Ariel?
-൧ില്‍. പണ്ട ഷീല. - ഷീല?
Ariel?
൧ഥില?
That's kind of pretty. OK. Ariel.
ചാതി ണന. ൭ ൧്ഥില.
Now's your moment
൨൭൧ നട.
Floating in a blue lagoon
7ലഭ്യാഥറ്റ വ്‌ 'ല്ഥഥഗ.
Boy, you better do it soon
൧൨൧൭ ൧൭൧ ൭൧ ൧൧൭! ലോ.
No time will be better
74ഒറ്ട ന ഒട) ഷഥറ്റ (ലാ77 ലവ്വ്‌.
She don't say a word
൧൭ (൭: ഥാ ഒഥ൭-൭൧൭.
And she won't say a word until ya kiss the girl
ഥു വ്ഒ ഗ്ര (ര൭ ഒഠ൭-ഒ്രാദ ലോറ (ഭഒഥ ല്ഥന ൨൭.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la Don't be scared
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 പററ ഒ.
You got the mood prepared Go on and kiss the girl
7൭൧ റ ഒറ്ട ടട വ്ടഠവ്ഒക൨. ൧6൭൦, വ്ഗഥ(ണ ൨൭.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la Don't stop now
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 പററ ലലാ ടല്ര7ഥറ.
Don't try to hide it how you wanna kiss the girl
പററ ൨൧൭ ടലഗഠ്ഥറ്റ്‌ ലഷ്‌ (൭൧ 0൭ ലഗ്ന ൧ ഗഒഥ7ഒ.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la Float along
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 77൧ഥ്‌൭ ഥലടഖനഒ.
And listen to the song
ഥു ഹറ 9റ൮൧.
Song say kiss the girl
2 ഒറു (ക൭ വഗ ശവ 4൧.
Sha-la-la-la-la-la Music play
൭൧൭-(9-(9-49-49-(9 77 ഥലന്ന.
Do what the music say You gotta kiss the girl
൧൧൦ ഒ )൭ഥറ നഷ്‌. കഥ നട്ട വ്ഥ്ന ഗവ്‌ 7.
Kiss the girl
വഗ്സ്‌ഒ വ്ഒ.
- Why don't you - Kiss the girl?
- (രഥട്യാദ (൭൧ (൭൧൧൭. - ലഗ്ന ഗവ ഥ്‌
Go on and kiss the girl
൧6൦, വ്ഗഥണ൦ ഗഒഥ൭ ൧.
- Go on and... - Kiss the girl
- ഒ്ധങിലി 0... - ഠി ഠഒ.
Hang on, I've got ya.
ഥാ, ടവ ൭ ഠ്ല്വാദ ത്വ.
Nice work, boys. That was a close one. Too close.
ദ്വവാദിപത്ധ ടണ്ഡമ. വധ ഠ്ല്ന്മന്ഥാന്ല.. ബ്വലാണ്ട.
The little tramp. She's better than I thought.
൭ ൪൭൦ ബ്ടിന്. 1ലാവാലിറ്ദ്ഥാഠ്മു വ്വ ടയ.
Well, at this rate, he'll be kissing her by sunset for sure.
ദ്രിദ്ധ ലാ, ഠി ടക നലഘ്ധന്സ നല്ലാ നദ്ല്ഘ് ദ്ധ, ന്ധ.
Well, it's time Ursula took matters into her own tentacles.
൧ ട്വാട! നടടാസ് ഭി നലമ്നാഒ്ബി ല്വാബാലാലില്വ.
Triton's daughter will be mine. And then I'll make him writhe.
ഗ്ന ലിത്ബ്യടഠി ൩॥9വ. ന്ധ മഡാധമ ഠി നന്യാടിലാല.
I'll see him wriggle like a worm on a hook.
ചവ ടിക്ല നമ ഠി നന്മ നടന ദേ ഠി നമ്മ ൭.
Eric? If l may say,
50 [യിദ്ധിട ടഭ്വാഠില്വിത്ട,
far better than any dream girl is one of flesh and blood,
൮ 1ലാ10 ലിബ്ര റ3ഠിട സ്ഥി 1ദില്സ൭ന൭ ടട ട൦ഠിറ്നാ ോദ്ബിന്മ,
one warm and caring and right before your eyes.
൮ നട്ട ്ബാനണാല്ടടന ൦ ഠി ല്ലാ നദ്ദ ത്വ.
Ariel.
൧ഥില.
Ariel, wake up. I just heard the news. Congratulations.
൧൧, നാഥ. ഡാ ന്യു ലാല. 1ല്ന്്ല.
Kiddo, we did it.
ഗ്ലാ, ന
What is this idiot babbling about?
1111111111
Right, as if you two didn't know.
ഗീഠഠണിദ്വിത്ധാല്ധാ ടിവല്ഡ.
The whole town's buzzin' about the prince gettin’ hitched this afternoon.
ല്ധഡ്വാ്ലഘാംവന്മണാ 0 ിത്വാല്ബണാ ൩.
You know, he's getting married.
ദ്ധ ല്ഡ, ഠി മിഖ്വ്്നയ്ന.
You silly side-walker. I just wanted to wish ya luck.
ദ്ധ ടി ാഠഠഠസൃന്ു ലു) ടു. എവ ന്ല്ലോത്ഥ ടലണട്‌.
I'll catch ya later. I wouldn't miss it.
എഡ്ൃധ്വായ്ധ നമി. എവ ലിഗന്്ഡ്ന്യാല്ന.
Well, now, Eric.
8ം॥ില, 50൦.
It appears that l was mistaken.
പും സ്ഥാലിസ൭ മവ ഠ്‌ ടിദ്യാ.
This mystery maiden of yours does, in fact, exist.
ബ്‌ സ്ട്ലി ദ്ധ ടലാലസ്മ നണമന്യ 99.
And she is lovely.
ഉ ഠദ ടഥ്ാാധിറ ണിം
Congratulations, my dear.
ചന്ന, ടത.
We wish to be married as soon as possible.
വ്രണ നല്ഡ ലിയ ടലലാ്‌ സ്ധഘാ!ന്൩.
Yes, of course, Eric, but these things do take time, you know.
൭, പധ ടയ, 501൦, ദ്വ ൩ നന്ന നട, ദ്വ ലിസ.
This afternoon, Grimsby. The wedding ship departs at sunset.
ലബ്ബ, ണ്നടിമു്വാല ാലിയ്സ്്ന്ന റാലിലാടട നടാ നമ്മ ബ്ബ.
Very well, Eric, as you wish.
ഒറ, ലം, ബന്ജ്യത്ധ.
What a lovely little bride I'll make
൧൦റെറുറഗക്ഥറ്റ ട്‌ ഒധ ൭൭൧൭൨.
My dear, I'll look divine
കദൃഭ്ഥറ്ധ ഒധ ഒക (കഥഗടഥ ൧ലട5൦7.
Things are working out according to my ultimate design
ട്ലനഥഒഥ)൭ -ദെറററ 77ന്‌ ലോല ൬൭൧൮ ൭:൨ 7ഥഗമഥറ്റത്ഥ.
Soon I'll have that little mermaid
7ഒലനട (ഒറ്‌ ൭ധ ഒക്ഥ റ്ട്രാദ റ്ഥഥറ 7൧.
And the ocean will be mine
ഥു (ഗ്രെ ഒക്ഥ൭൨൪്‌ ൩00൨.
The sea witch. Oh, no. She's gonna... gotta...
ട। ഡിഡ്ബടഥ്്. ഠ൩൨൨9ലെ൦. ൧19 1൮൨... മവ നല.
Ariel.
൧ഥില.
Ariel, was flying. Of course, I was flying.
൧൧, മവ ടലി ണു. “ല്വ ടലല്‍യ॥।, മവ ടി 0൭.
l saw the watch.
ചവ നന്വാഠ്ധ്ഡ ബ്.
The witch was watching the mirror,
ഉധിഡ്ഖ ടി നടന ലേന്ന്ന,
and she was singin’ with a stolen set of pipes.
൦ ഠി നബി" ബു ധനു ഠേ.
Do you hear what I'm tellin’ you?
ദ്ധ ബോല്‌ ല്ലാ വര്മ?
The prince is marrying the sea witch in disguise.
11:11 11] റ്ധിഡ്ബിദധ്വത്ാ നബ.
- Are you sure about this? - Have I ever been wrong?
- രവ 350 ന്മ ബ്‌? - ഉനട്വിയി ലിവ ടിന?
I mean, when it's important?
[ഗീഭ്ധഠിവ, 019 ലാലിഖസവാല്ന്യ?
What are we gonna do?
൧൧ ന്൯ നലധ്ധ്റ
Before the sun sets on the third day.
ട്ലാല്ഗ്ന ഗനദഒഗഥ്‌൭(൧ഥ ൧൭൭9 7൭7 (കറ0൭ഒ.
Ariel, grab onto that.
൧൧ിലി, ലലലാ 0൭ ൮.
Flounder, get her to that boat as fast as your fins can carry you.
നാലാ ഠി ഭവാല്ല്ഡ്ധ ടലലാബ്യാ ട്റ്രാ।ത്ധാഠില്വാദമ.
I'l try.
൧൮ ടിക്ന ഡീ.
I gotta get to the sea king. He must know about this.
൧൮ നട്ട്‌ ലയ! ൫ വദ. ൧19 നടട॥ ല്ഡ ന്മ ബ്‌.
- What about me? What about me? - You.
- ളമ്റുല്നടന്മ ഠ്യ ലിവ? - രവ.
Find a way to stall that wedding.
ചില്ല ധന്ധിം നിത്ബ്വാലിയ്സ്്ന്മ്ന്ലധ.
Stall the wedding. What am I?
റസി ലിവ്‌. ചവ ബി ല്ലാ?
What? That's it.
൧൧൭൮ ഠ19.
Move it. Let's go. We got an emergency here.
8ലുല്ഖിറില. ഷയ്‌. [ഗ്മ 39 ഭണടടന ഠി ടി.
Dearly beloved...
ണാ ഠിടക...
Don't worry, Ariel. We're gonna make it.
പദാ, ൧ഥില. 19016൨.
We're almost there.
ഉ അന്വ ഠി ട്ട.
Yes, do you, Eric, take Vanessa...
൭, ഒഠില്വ്്‌നത്ധ, 561൦, നലിനട ഗ്ലടടടാ...
to be your lawfully wedded wife
നല] ട്ലിന്ധു്ണാ ടട
for as long as you both shall live?
ടലാദു്ു നആിത്ധാണ്ധദ?
Ido.
ദയ ലിന.
It being... And do you...
ഉസ... ൧00 ഠിഷ്വിത്ഖ...
- Then by the power vested in me... - Get away from me, you slimy...
- ഠില്സ്ധ ഠ്ബുണിവടടാദഠ്ലിവ... -ങ്റി ഠ്ലി മവ, ത്ധവ ഥന്ന്സഖം..
Why, you little...
(രന്വാമ, ന്ധ ടി ഈ...
- Ariel? - Eric.
- ഷീല? - 50൦.
You can talk?
!ദ്ധാഠില്വാലയലിത്വാ?
- You're the one. - Eric, get away from her.
-ര്ര്ധിട ഒ. - £0ല്ട്ധ്വത്ന ഠി ത്വ ഠ്്സുഒ.
- It was you all the time. - Eric, l wanted to tell you.
- ധ്യാ ധ്ധ ടല ല്‍. - 50൦, മിവ നല്വാലില്ഡ ത്വ.
Eric, no.
50൦൭൦൩.
You're too late.
ദ്ധ ഠ്ല്വ്ലിദ്മ്‌.
So long, lover boy.
ലന്‌ ന്ന്യാടി, ൧൨ഠ്ല്ലക്യടി.
- Ariel. - Poor little princess.
- ഷില്‍. - ടിന ാധ്ലി ഭ്വ്ദഡ.
It's not you I'm after. I've a much bigger fish to...
ദധിയ്സുഖ്ധവ ല്വ നല്ഡ. ൧൭ ॥॥യ൭൦൩ല്സു്ബാലാവ്പാടട്...
Ursula, stop.
പ്രവി, ലാലി.
Why, King Triton. How are you?
൨, ല്യം ൩൯൦൩. ച്യാദന്ദ്ധാല?
- Let her go. - Not a chance. She's mine now.
- [1 ല്ാമടിന്വ ഠ1ഒ. - 151 ടലയ. ൧ ന॥॥ഠവ ടല.
- We made a deal. - Daddy, I'm sorry.
ദ്ര 510 ലുദ്ബി. കൃ, നടലീത്ന ടമ.
I didn't mean to. I didn't know.
ദയ മഗധ ലാ. കട ടിനല്സ.
You see?
ദ്ധ നലന്വാട്റ
The contract's legal, binding and completely unbreakable,
ധന്തിസ 5൭. 0॥യ, ഠ൩ടിലാംിലല്‍ ഠ്രാട്വിത്ഥ ടണം ടലി,
even for you.
ദ്ധ 0൧ ധസ്ധിലത്ധ.
Of course, I always was a girl with an eye for a bargain.
ല്വ ടലല്‍യ॥।, മവ ടട ാലഭ്ഥാധന ൮ ട്ടം നല്ലി ബില ൮ബാവാദലിം
The daughter of the great sea king
വലി വദ്ര വാട്ട
is a very precious commodity.
13ല ടബാജാവണ ല്മ്ണഃ.
But I might be willing to make an exchange
ലവ സ്ഥാന ന്മ്ഡ നന്ബ്ധമ്‌' ഹല്ധിഖ്്
for someone even better.
ധ്ധിം ട്വ ില്‍ാ്സാലി
Eric, what are you doing?
50൦, ൭ ദ്ധാധമ?
Grim, I lost her once. I'm not gonna lose her again.
ന, ടവ ൭൩ വിണു ഠദ ടട്യി. എവ ലിഗനല്ഡ ബ ഠ്ധ്ഘ!.
Now, do we have a deal?
ലിയ്വു, 09 ദഠ9 ഹലുദ്ിക്ന്‌?
It's done then.
പ്ഠില്൩വിദ്ധവാഘ്റ്ധ.
Your Majesty.
വമ്ബിവ.
Daddy.
ഷു.
- At last, it's mine. - No.
- ചിന്ന, ടവ ൭1 ഠ്ല്വാദ. - 11991൦
You.
ദ്വ.
You monster.
ദ്ധഘസ്വ.
Don't fool with me, ya little brat.
പനാ നല്ന-ന്ദ്ന ഠന്യേമ്ബ്വ, ധ്വ ടി ഭി.
Contract or no, I'll blast...
ഠ്വ 1ഠ്ച മിവ ലിയാ...
- Why, you little fool. - Eric. Eric, look out.
- (രനല്വാദ, ദ്വ ടി 100൦1൨. - 50൦. 51൦, ലല)95-9952.
After him.
ദ്യ ഠിഒ.
Come on.
ഷുഡ്‌.
Say goodbye to your sweetheart.
പ്്ലോ ടലണമ ന്നാ ഭ്യാഠ്ഃ ടക സ്വ.
Babies. My poor little poopsies.
൧ഗി്്ല്ലരടിമ് മന്ല-ന്ല്ലഭംി॥വ.
- Eric, you've gotta get away from here. - No, I won't leave you.
- 60൦, യവ നടട॥ 0 ഠി ടി. - 00൭൦ മിവ ലിറ ാടലിത്ിത്ധ.
You pitiful, insignificant fools.
ദ്ധ ടി ാഠഠഠസൃണാ നടടന്മ.
Look out.
പ്്൮ു2-992.
Now I am the ruler of all the ocean.
ലയ്വനാ വ ജ്വി്ധ്്ന.
The waves obey my every whim.
ഠമ്പാലിഗലിയ്ഥ നനണദ്ധ്ല്‍ി ടവ.
Eric.
50൦.
The sea and all its spoils bow to my power.
[ഥി ൦ ടല്ുട്ദട്സു ടിക ഡഥഠ്ധ്ലര്ാഠ്ഃ വ.
Eric.
50൦.
So much for true love.
ല്റ്ധില ടസ്ഡബസട ധസ്ധിറ്ന്മ ധി.
She really does love him, doesn't she, Sebastian?
൧1 നന്യ സ്ലിം, ധിത്വിയി ലാവ, ടലോടട്ലണ്‌?
Well, it's like l always say, Your Majesty,
ല്യാല ൮൭0൧ ടു ടലല്ധ ഖം, സ്വ്ബിവ,
children got to be free to lead their own lives.
വ്വലിറിഖന്ലഗനടട്ലില്വാലാമട ധന്ധിനലട[ധിത്ഥ ര്വഠ്ധോാദ്ന നലിയ.
You always say that?
ദ്ധ ടലല്ധ യദ ഥലൃബ?
Then I guess there's just one problem left.
പഠി ടവ ടഃ ബ൭ ടബ്ബ നടി.
And what's that, Your Majesty?
ഉ ല്വാലിവ്ധ, സബ്ബ്‌?
How much I'm going to miss her.
ദറുല്നന്മ മവ ടിക്ന നല്ഥഠ്ധ്സ.
Yes.
ഒ.
Thank you.
ലന മടി.
Il love you, Daddy.
ദയ ടമിയ്ത്ധ, കയ.
Now we can walk Now we can run
ലഭ 7ഗ്ട 2൧0(൭൨ ഥലഡലര്യാ. ക്ലഭ്ഒറ്റ 7ഗ്ട 20(൭൨ ൧ലഒ൧7.
Now we can stay aif day in the sun
കലഭഒററ്റ 7ഗ്ട 2൧0(൭൨ ട്ലാക്ധ്റെ റ്(ഒന ഒഗദൃയഭ നദഗക്ഥ്‌.
Just you and me
൧9൧൮൭ (൭൧ റ്റെ ൭:൨.
And ican be
ഥുഒ്ണ ഒ ൧ഠ൦ 9൨.
Part of your world
്ലാദഗടറ്റ്‌റെ റ്ഗ്ാദറ്ട റ്ഥഒ൩൧.